behargaming: sup
rkxbz: hi
00warl0k00: hello big fan of you
LlNUX: <3
Protoxus: Hello :)
st47ik: Hi George VoHiYo
foxubu: Nooo RegEx 🙈🙈🙈
st47ik: Hi Chat
st47ik: Regex PogChamp
lefse: REEEEEEEEEEEgex
m1k1b_: hi
Protoxus: RegEx is nice
LlNUX: shit i pronounce it wrong too
WinterLabyrinth: Hello
speeddrawing101: YEEEEEEESSSSS
iagia: sup nerds
malg0d: Green tea
felixth7: whas up
halldorvalberg: SeemsGood
aa_ato: NoFrindDoDay:
QuantumComputingMIT: First
FaustPetrovich: hey
malg0d: No quantum here
lefse: No matter how you pronouce it, it does the same job Kappa
lasercatboss: lasercatboss subscribed with Twitch Prime. They've subscribed for 2 months! why
malg0d: I'm a l33t god that codes dank regex magic
LlNUX: stackoverflow does my regex for me most the time
FaustPetrovich: FaustPetrovich subscribed at Tier 1.
haircutjimmy: Afternoon @georgehotz. Regex, hey? Glutton for punishment!
loaffy_: i hate regex
virgoshlok: Hi
krakendmp: hi
blakeswelt: !uptime
eax_ebx: Привет.
szalalala: Hi @georgehotz !
johnny_thehobo: is this how we hack nasa?
jsanxez: it is
haircutjimmy: regex101.com
Shahin8520: i guess you forget newline character?
Protoxus: 1 @haircutjimmy
f_karamazov: Ex > regex
macrib02: is it to easy?
m1k1b_: try to put 4 dots in the beggining, maybe that is the problem
erk4sh: hello, in which country are you
jsanxez: I want to learn to hack :/
foxubu: We need AI to automatically generate the RegEx :D
f_karamazov: Why do you need the $
Vilebiscuit: Hello, I am planning on starting learning machine learning. what do you guys propose I do first
itsChoudhry: @Vilebiscuit predict something
marsroger44: whats up boys
marsroger44: what are we doing today
awesomeo113: @vilebiscuit udemy probably isn’t a bad resource
Vilebiscuit: maybe udacity?
krakendmp: datacamp is ok
hmnvdota: they should know you know regex
itsChoudhry: @Vilebiscuit Do you care about the Math or just application using prebuilt algorithms?
coProof: Yay not coq thing
litesam: That guy from destroyallsoftware has made https://www.executeprogram.com/ which is a good source to learn RegEx
dawgwhisper007: stupid is as stupid does
hmnvdota: @litesam wat guy?
litesam: Gary Bernhardt
Avelansh: anyone remmber 'Wat' video from destroyallsoftware
alexlucas_: yo
alexlucas_: alexlucas_ subscribed with Twitch Prime. They've subscribed for 3 months!
litesam: I thing first 30 days is free
iyilik: Hi I love you
haircutjimmy: regex101.com @georgehotz !
Vilebiscuit: @itsChoudhry No I care about math too
forkdb: Hello George
winnyXE: maybe its а not a
coProof: payoDance
forkdb: I might become your sub, once, I get my new debit card...
cccnrd: someone knows a thing like hack.hands?
forkdb: Am glad you are back online on twitch
SlaterUSA: all answers are, in the end, wrong.
SlaterUSA: /deep
alreye: sup buddy. Emacs user here :)
hmnvdota: TTours
yoyo_brobro: doctorHEART doctorHEART doctorHEART
Protoxus: @slaterusa Then that answer is wrong too. Congratulations, you just created a paradox.
sa7b: LesbianPride
foxubu: Is that NoScript in his Chrome? :o
coProof: Truuuuu
ImJ4Gu4R: halo halo halo
itsChoudhry: @Vilebiscuit Then the road is a little longer, but the bare minimum is Andrew ng machine learning course. For the math then just look up frameworks on how to applly the theory you learn't in the course, but I also used umdey and books to learn about where to apply what and where what algorithm make sense and how to work out which one to use
herrmuckelmann: can you move the window to the right a bit?
LeadCoder: im coming for you george
Bombapil0t: MrDestructoid
herrmuckelmann: the cam is blocking stuff
BryanSWAGBEAST: we cant see
Shahin8520: can you put the browser a little bit to the right, so we can see it ? thakns
alreye: What's a good resource to stay up today with computer science news?
Protoxus: ^
ImJ4Gu4R: yea, pls adjust that cam
Santiago_LHC: Regex Sunday! Yay
ImJ4Gu4R: Ahh regex cam
coProof: Slow down and pay attention to us!
BryanSWAGBEAST: Adjust Cam bro!
Bombapil0t: yikes
Protoxus: @alreye Not sure, but I use Ars Digita
ImJ4Gu4R: slow down brah, cam pls
unknown_elemen: how is evry one doing
krakendmp: move the windows pls
BryanSWAGBEAST: lmao @georgehotz fix cam
Santiago_LHC: Why should he move to windows
Protoxus: @santiago_lhc Because we can't see the terminal he's typing in
krakendmp: yeah
Santiago_LHC: Ah, THE window, I thought the OS
ImJ4Gu4R: maybe he means window is cam
coProof: Yeah move to the boot amp partition on your Mac lol
alreye: @Protoxus Doesn't appear on google. What's the website?
data_day_life: Jebaited
BryanSWAGBEAST: fix cam
ImJ4Gu4R: Alright, so i can continue my sub
BryanSWAGBEAST: lmao nobody could stop him
rupan3: do you want to be a webdev?
Protoxus: @alreye Oh sorry, I remembered wrong, it's Ars Technica
alreye: @Protoxus thanks
syska: [a-z]
StupidGladiator: @rupan3 you have to be crazy to go from the world of machin learning and mathematics to the world of web, so boring ResidentSleeper
Protoxus: @alreye You're welcome :)
Santiago_LHC: Gotta know some Regex though
rupan3: StupidGladiator hehe
ImJ4Gu4R: Does anyone know how to do picture in picture in twitch?
0verclass: hi legendary hacker
ckk0t0: Increase font. I’m blind
鼻史: genius
ckk0t0: Please
Vilebiscuit: @itsChoudhry Thanks a lot man
Julianhgg: my idol
ckk0t0: Cool man. Thanks
Santiago_LHC: Detecting links is hard
frediiiez: can you zoom the browser a bit?
crazywulf770: oh nice i love regex what is he doin?
Santiago_LHC: Learning, apparently
Bacon4Life_: is this a 4k monitor?
frediiiez: noooo
gseven_: 5k i think
Santiago_LHC: 78k
Bacon4Life_: holy shit
ckk0t0: Now i can’t read it.
gseven_: its LG ultrafine 5k i think
ㄱ_니은: crawling lesson
crazywulf770: i can recommend https://rubular.com/ its my favourite to prepare regex
Avelansh: crawling web 101
Satanicus7: hows your keyboard doing man?
ImJ4Gu4R: Picture in picture mode, type on your web console. document.querySelector("div.highwind-video-player > div > video").requestPictureInPicture()
arxenixOW: regexr.com is the best imo
swagettiyolonaise69: no cock today ?
litesam: Why George is not in Twitter?
Bacon4Life_: monkaS
supnerdstv: do i get mod if i say i like the keyboard?
rupan3: what keyboard?
Plurmorant: @litesam twitter is worse than heroin
Bombapil0t: follow him on instagram @litesam
3310: StupidGladiator , Regex is only for the web ... Pepega
Santiago_LHC: Keyboard talk gets you banned
GustaveTXC: hi
alreye: @georgehotz We want to see you do these challenges in C
Protoxus: @arxenixow That's the one I use too
speeddrawing101: yea shut up Charlie lol
ImJ4Gu4R: Dark mode anyone?
ImJ4Gu4R: My eyes is burning
foxubu: @litesam He is but he does not use it @realGoergeHotz
syska: wat s keyborad
Bogz75: use regexr website for regex help
ckk0t0: Dark mode make it better. Can’t see shit
krakendmp: a keyboard called borad
shutchie: @georgehotz line 3 error
Shahin8520: because you didnt close the parentesis above in re.compile
Santiago_LHC: He tried Dark mode in another stream, didn't like it.
zthreee: Line 3
litesam: In JavaScript you have String.match() which will all the matches in a array
GustaveTXC: what programming language is?
Bombapil0t: i didn't see the tea once today?
Shahin8520: line 3 re.compile parenthesis
zthreee: Line 3 missing closing )
shutchie: @georgehotz on match line. Line 3 dude
zthreee: SeemsGood
GustaveTXC: VoHiYo
Attlantiz_: what are you doing today george? learning regex?
jellyjar: got called out for not knowing regex at work, or here?
Attlantiz_: CoolStoryBob
GustaveTXC: Squid1 Squid2 Squid3 Squid4
serohh: Regex is sooo boring
Bacon4Life_: PogChamp
Avraewyn: EZ Clap
Attlantiz_: regex is gud and useful
litesam: Use https://regexper.com/ which will show the Regular Expression in an State diagram
alreye: @georgehotz We want to see you do these challenges in C
crazywulf770: <3 gogogo <3 regex <3
HopZe: True
Attlantiz_: lmao st peterson
Shahin8520: True
HopZe: St peterson?
Bombapil0t: never thought that way
Attlantiz_: The man himself, st peterson
rupan3: saint peter you heahtnes
abk467: can't argue with that
C4TFive: im just gunna go to hell
sausainismilka: what is the color of your keyboard? LUL Kappa
fghoekstra79: i would love to see you take an IQ test on here imGlitch
dr_koili: Stan Peterson
Attlantiz_: cant argue with st peterson
dr_cashews: st peters son
rupan3: what switches?
Shahin8520: .
Attlantiz_: no keyboard questions ffs
GustaveTXC: Squid1 Squid2 Squid3 Squid2 Squid4
0verclass: only i can see is 'welcome to the dark side!' lol
litesam: See the power of https://regexper.com/ ya'll gonna love it!
visudo20179c: so what is geohot doing today
0verclass: thanks @litesam
Attlantiz_: learning regex
Santiago_LHC: Well done
visudo20179c: good job George
GustaveTXC: PowerUpR SabaPing PowerUpL
Bacon4Life_: 200 iq
sausainismilka: one mistake can mean a lot.
crazywulf770: nice to have a stream where i understand what he is doing :-D
Attlantiz_: Kappa
Attlantiz_: true
frediiiez: have you seen Mr. Robot?
fghoekstra79: i think his IQ is high. would love to see him solve those problems
Iliftmymousealot: in my fourth semester compiler construction exam I had to write a jflex and antlr rule to match Letter Salutations I still have ptsd because of that exam question
forkdb: How can you practice when you feel really sad because you are not able to solve problems?! ... please explain
Zabak378: dont you need double / ?
mltsd: @forkdb coffee :P
Santiago_LHC: "Stop being a n00b" - George Hotz, 2019
Bacon4Life_: just exercise 4Head
Harm133: LUL
visudo20179c: if at first you don't succeed, try again
forkdb: Ok thanks
frediiiez: LUL
visudo20179c: while noob do end
saurabhshinde: c or python ?? for competitive coding ??
cerrad1234: python
cerrad1234: cython
Santiago_LHC: competitive coding of what?
Luccaasss: JAVASCRIPT
sausainismilka: if you not noob you can solve this
crazywulf770: maybe its too greedy try .*?
sausainismilka: hacker rank:N00B
visudo20179c: true coders don't need to compete
sausainismilka: just kidding
0verclass: both are good at solve problem i think
lostshiya: Hong Kong is on edge, university slaughter can happen https://twitter.com/nathanlawkc/status/1196099979854712832
Luccaasss: c is the best
cerrad1234: just make an ai for solving these problems?
MatiGoG: ?gnisu eh si draobyek tahw
litesam: Beers - Front Bottoms
balzak43: the r prefix denotes a raw string btw
grizvok: @cerrad1234 yeah that's totally trivial!
Santiago_LHC: @lostshiya I very much doubt it could happen.
Harm133: why dont you use dark mode
balzak43: means you can use the backslash without escaping it
balzak43: so instead of \
0verclass: dance time
zoki_macola: pee time
sausainismilka: that walk tho
Bombapil0t: pee & tea
Santiago_LHC: He don't like dark mode on hackerrank
krakendmp: :D
Luccaasss: because he is of the light
kanogger: lolll
mltsd: @MatiGoG gnihtemos ro draobyek rekcah ekil gnihtemos
Bombapil0t: sony said so @Luccaasss
forkdb: Can anyone answer... how is he so good at coding?!
kerlanT: that runescape related video e.e
mltsd: @forkdb i think hes been coding a while
litesam: @forkdb Practice
kanogger: @forkdb he started when he was 3 years old and his brain is twice as big as a normal human
jrrbls: He drinks 4 liters of green tea a day
jrrbls: That's the secret
jrrbls: And mate
oMythra: Whats up Georgey boi
forkdb: Haha
Iliftmymousealot: green tea or ice coffee?
crazywulf770: jrrbls good idea i need more green tea :-D
mltsd: does anyone know how many teabags of black tea are safe to drink per day? Trying to quit coffee
litesam: Where is your old mini-piano?
kanogger: @mltsd try adderal it's healthier
forkdb: I do not think it is because of tea...
kanogger: Kappa
forkdb: It is a gift!!
mltsd: @kanogger too expensive :P
johnny_thehobo: geo you dont know me but i love you buddy
johnny_thehobo: remember that
cakalbaris: regex101.com make it easier
jrrbls: weirdo
litesam: Where is your Piano?
crystoobaal: !uptime
forkdb: I feel sad when he runs tests and few fail.. I feel likewise when I practice on hackerank
midnightbytes: hello just found out about you.Awesome work. i m very happy that you stream
data_day_life: regex101 . com
BlLL: are you living in a tiny house?
PushUpek84: regex101 ;]
data_day_life: you'll prob like it better
FargioFarmani: do you code every day? @georgehotz
nautzz: regex101 is quite a bit better
jellyjar: regex101 is the best
BlLL: PogChamp
TM876: LUL
cakalbaris: i was told you dude
Rekkeno: regexbeast lul
crazywulf770: https://rubular.com/r/9g4DryZ55MGw2S
GGGrimmy: Can't wait until he figures out that regex is different in literally every language
GGGrimmy: :D
MDK1980: I have no fucking idea what's going on D:
data_day_life: @MDK1980 we matching generic patterns in strings
scorpiocyborg: for one time I understand what he is doing :p
grizvok: @MDK1980 regex...nothing crazyt
MDK1980: @data_day_life I've literally never coded a single second before. But have to say, this is mesmerizing...
nautzz: (?=) is the way to do it
litesam: If you complete this HackerRank play a song in Piano!!
nautzz: need to make a non capturing group
crazywulf770: @georgehotz .* star is greedy you it matches the string until the last situation where the regex would match... if you do .*? it matches until the first match
data_day_life: @MDK1980 in this case, it's similar to scraping a webpage and extracting (called capturing in regex) links in the html source
GGGrimmy: @georgehotz python has support for non-greedy "star" match also
crazywulf770: no just add a ?
Zheikk3: Can you talk about your time at CMU ? Thinking about going there next year
nesbyy1: PogChamp
cakalbaris: <a href="(.*?)">(.*?)</a> isnt work ?
Nryqt: heya
不好意思: Pog
forkdb: Apparently, this is not as easy as hacking... just kidding...
nesbyy1: ^ do*
litesam: Play Piano after completing this challenge.
iammrrob0t: Cheer100
dorkmo: Party1
Jadess: @georgehotz how long till we get level 5 autonomous vehicles on roads
anguscupcake: Why do you use a Mac?
Zheikk3: @Jadess not in our lifetime
okurcozer: Hey george
Jadess: @zheikk3 my prof says the same. I'm triggered
forkdb: So... what do you do to unwind?!
YouPowerRush: ayy lamo
Santiago_LHC: @anguscupcake why not?
quelsarprime: what is the blue window. I can't read it.
anguscupcake: @Santiago_LHC can't upgrade them
Santiago_LHC: @anguscupcake to what?
MuscleMario: What's happenin?
forkdb: Yes.. exactly.. this is why I keep loosing my hackos all the ti,e....
Abo7atm: WHAT! How long has he been live?
data_day_life: / srpski ?
forkdb: Why does he keep his index finger on his forehead... ?!
yamchah2: !uptime
gseven_: !uptime
MuscleMario: Anyone here been at QCon?
Abo7atm: !uptime
data_day_life: @forkdb channeling that third eye energy
Santiago_LHC: @anguscupcake What do you need hardware upgrades for on a computer for coding?
anguscupcake: can't upgrade any component without paying Apple $200 for 16gb of ram
Zheikk3: me :)
euranymous: hi clean shaved George
forkdb: 1uptime
forkdb: !uptime
crazywulf770: @georgehotz i think you overthinking this one... try a more simple one https://rubular.com/r/lOP4VJDJhW3bS8
data_day_life: @forkdb 58 minutes
kkteja: !uptime
Santiago_LHC: @anguscupcake so what? You buy with as much RAM as you need, problem solved.
data_day_life: data_day_life subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 2 months! platyGG platyGG platyGG platyGG platyGG
euranymous: What are you working on @georgehotz ?
MuscleMario: recently I learned [sS] instead of trying to do (.)* for new lines too. b/c some regex's dont support multiline parsing. Hurrdurr
forkdb: @data_day_life Thank you
Lefer_: Ohayou Geohot san VoHiYo uyuyuySmile
forkdb: Hello gundu
Akash_44: Pog
whichtom: easy
Kuunih: Pog
anguscupcake: it's a problem because if you ever decide to code something intensive down the line, you have to buy a whole new one. same thing as buying game consoles, it's wasteful
data_day_life: platyLILB platyLILB platyLILB
Santiago_LHC: TWITCHCOQ!
whichtom: eyy twitchcoq
MuscleMario: oh no, back to the coq
crazywulf770: shit
forkdb: Hey... please talk about something interesting...
bcrscahh198987: Any place to do regex exercises?
Santiago_LHC: @anguscupcake So it's not for you. Clearly it's more than good enough for plenty of people
data_day_life: i mean if you're running unity then maybe that's true.... but if you're not then.... why not use the cloud @anguscupcake ?
0verclass: dat speed
anguscupcake: That's why I want to know why he uses one, what advantages are there?
forkdb: Man... I wish I had half of his skills ....
warpoit: morning geo happy coding
Santiago_LHC: @anguscupcake MacOS I imagine
data_day_life: @anguscupcake it runs on top of ubuntu
bcrscahh198987: Self proclaimed regex beast, sure thing georgie
Jadess: bamboM
Sarcazeem: ScaredyCat
data_day_life: @anguscupcake but windows now has support for linux subsystem ... and then there's docker so.... it's kind of moot
psychicside: is this a size font for ants?
bcrscahh198987: regex101 is the best website IMO
bcrscahh198987: for regex
data_day_life: agreed
vincexviii: regex PepeLaugh
jmc516: Do you have ur RegEx license tho
bcrscahh198987: you need a license to use RegEx, damn that's new
bcrscahh198987: Probably need a license to type on a keyboard
jmc516: Nah it's a meme
MuscleMario: Geohot, do you believe in the hype behind WebAssembly. 'Bytecode Alliance'. Idea is that they are trying to take wasm outside the browser and also agree on a set of standards for the 'NEW FUTURE STDLIB' equivalent. U drinkin this kool-aid, cuz I am hype about this.
residentsleeperrrrrrrrr: why the FUCK do you use chrome.
reduf: could be domain1.domain2.domain3....
reduf: also could be domain1 without any .com
Ziv0: emails can have underscores dashes and pluses
reduf: and dot
crazywulf770: easy one
crazywulf770: :-)
Bacon4Life_: emails can have .com.xx
Rudolfkeil: Not using dark mode? U monster
bcrscahh198987: I don't think the website offers dark mode
MuscleMario: chrome://flags -> forced dark mode
crazywulf770: Bacon4Life_ yeah real email regex are much more complex
pogu: I think most peopel just google email regex and copy it over. It's pretty big iirc
NoLimitFitness: What are we doing?
crazywulf770: pogu ^^
NoLimitFitness: tsodinJS tsodinJS ?
crazywulf770: python regexing basics
NoLimitFitness: nice
serhejenos: serhejenos subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 10 months!
LaheyFPS: good morning
LaheyFPS: yes
serhejenos: Hi everyone
Sarcazeem: Also mail servers accept sign @georgehotz
LaheyFPS: hello @serhejenos
euranymous: chew some ice for asmr effect
LaheyFPS: chew ice Kreygasm
MuscleMario: lol
YouPowerRush: here it cums
Bacon4Life_: go-army.america PogChamp
MonkaSupreme: put ice in nose Kreygasm
LiIDrunk: have you tried hands on WASD keyboard
euranymous: someone is geting a timeout
LaheyFPS: PogChamp Family show
residentsleeperrrrrrrrr: wheres the emotes
Sarcazeem: we gotta be appropriate as christian channel - chews ice
MuscleMario: Geohot -> Wasm -> Runtime outside of browser -> Bytecode Alliance trying to standardize the bytecode of the future (stdlib equivalent) -> hype or sham?
prvk3: you can show your tits though
crazywulf770: try a hard one
filipeoliveiraa: try a hard one
Vinndy: hey george please solve my hackerrank problem i'm stuck
crazywulf770: ^^
Sarcazeem: but in username field if there are sign a b@c.com and a c@c.com is same @georgehotz
Bacon4Life_: Are you ready to signup at go-army.america?
whichtom: regex is crazy man
directrix13: regex?(pert)
Abo7atm: George, Amazon just rejected my payment. What should I do with my life now?
Hunted9000: riPepperonis riPepperonis riPepperonis riPepperonis BlessRNG BlessRNG BlessRNG BlessRNG
euranymous: I listened to your album last night. It was amazing @georgehotz
MonkaSupreme: js
wall_streeter: are regular expressions reliable?
ragemaster999: did you study at an university?
r0kz_: :(
whichtom: rip twitchcoq
MonkaSupreme: do some multi line regex
FargioFarmani: try leetcode regex
LaheyFPS: I want your hoodie @georgehotz
euranymous: We need a discord channel!!!
directrix13: BNF > regex
MonkaSupreme: you could regex the twitch chat PogChamp
LaheyFPS: D:
Farafire: Farafire subscribed with Twitch Prime. They've subscribed for 2 months!
MuscleMario: I just ran away from regex
directrix13: lol
MuscleMario: parasing clojure project.clj EDN
LaheyFPS: regex is just regex LUL
MuscleMario: parsing*
VitalyzedTv: i never do regex :C
euranymous: regex is regex but you are breath taking
Abo7atm: What kind of grammars can regex express?
MuscleMario: Its basically pom.xml equivalent project.clj
root_user_198: install arch
directrix13: regex is a nice hacky little dsl
MuscleMario: Im super hype about wasm, but i dunno if i just drunk the kool aid
MuscleMario: >_<
ImNotTrolling: Do searches AI
MonkaSupreme: javascript expert
VitalyzedTv: PogChamp
fa_k: LUL
MonkaSupreme: Number()
vmarkushin: 0
directrix13: learn lodash after js
MuscleMario: lodash
MuscleMario: Dont do any of this lol
directrix13: Lodash
TheNakedFlame: LUL
Ziv0: LUL
plomlo12: true
TheNakedFlame: I'm so done with the shit-tastic ton of js frameworks that change every month
VitalyzedTv: why is he trolling this framework
VitalyzedTv: xD
MuscleMario: Bytecode Alliance Check it <-
forkdb: Hey George... please talk about something about your life, which you cherish
MuscleMario: let is a function scoped var
fa_k: Just write your own framework 4Head
MuscleMario: yeet
euranymous: JS is my first language BTW
MuscleMario: in will return an index to use
MuscleMario: of will return the value
Vinndy: let is blocked scoped not functon scoped
MuscleMario: for (x in coll)
th0rgam: you split
MuscleMario: fuck i goofed
Neven8775: String isn an array of Characters in JS so.. should be iterable
MuscleMario: for (x of coll)
ragemaster999: exposed on live stream
MuscleMario: for (x in coll)
fear_ep: try brainfuck @georgehotz
MuscleMario: includes
th0rgam: incuds
th0rgam: includes
euranymous: try brainfuck @georgehotz
zoki_macola: string doesnt have .forEach
MuscleMario: ^
MuscleMario: kappa ?
plomlo12: Are the speed comparisons in vanilla-js real numbers ?
MuscleMario: LOLOL
MonkaSupreme: you can do '123'.includes('1')
MuscleMario: just do regex .match(/regex/)
MonkaSupreme: in js you can do the /regex/ syntax PogChamp
MuscleMario: just slashes
directrix13: regex is built into JavaScript
MuscleMario: LOL
TheNakedFlame: FeelsAmazingMan REEEEEE
MuscleMario: AHHAHA
MonkaSupreme: PogChamp
i4cc8a9morw8kfrh: squadR
LaheyFPS: EZ
MuscleMario: im dying, afk
fear_ep: HahaHaha pog
nautzz: i want a friend who texts me "bro, sealand"
Ralph_124C_41: lol
scorpiocyborg: lol
i4cc8a9morw8kfrh: squadPepega
scorpiocyborg: this guy
forkdb: Really George... why are you learning js.. do you use it often?!
zeroeagle1: its just amerge sort I think
MuscleMario: b/c its simple skills
scorpiocyborg: he is evolving to his final form
vmarkushin: bro, clang
Vinndy: @georgehotz yo do this one it says ""hard"" https://www.hackerrank.com/contests/round-1-holiday-cup/challenges/biggest-slice/problem
nautzz: @forkdb It's A Meme
crazywulf770: better than metamath :-D
anguscupcake: react is a meme
jrrbls: Learn React Native
directrix13: @forkdb because JS is everywhere
ImNotTrolling: learn brainfuck @georgehotz
LaheyFPS: I hope its sweet tea
vmarkushin: Learn haskell plz
VitalyzedTv: is that water with ice? or iceatea with ice
MuscleMario: Google 'Bytecode Alliance' and validate my hype senpai
Ralph_124C_41: lol
ragemaster999: react harder :rage:
Zabak378: What do you guys think about PHP?
nautzz: the original reason behind the creation of brainfuck was kinda cool to me, its not interesting beyond that tho
zoki_macola: try Next.js
directrix13: Don't learn react, learn what it is based on: the functional programing language Elm
smurfd0: had a guest teacher in the univeristy who used BF, and he looked very tired ;)
zeroeagle1: why not web assembly?
MuscleMario: ^ That
hoffs: yeet it
leopp: did he uses screen or tmux?
i4cc8a9morw8kfrh: D:
mdrake_: im so triggered rn
MuscleMario: A framework for a framework my dawg
zerofuzzgiven: delete it
pogu: yes
TheNakedFlame: Framework-ception
anguscupcake: npm install npm
MuscleMario: apt get apt
scorpiocyborg: when is the new album dropping @georgehotz
pepino5: apt here we go!
Ralph_124C_41: this is actually causing me physical pain
LaheyFPS: LUL
anguscupcake: apt get gf
mdrake_: just gulp it 4Head
TheNakedFlame: FeelsAmazingMan All of them
ragemaster999: just script it 4Head
nautzz: The Future of Software...........
MuscleMario: Web
MuscleMario: Ass
GGGrimmy: And that's why no one should use macos :D
MuscleMario: ^
Caene: jokerd6Gold
MuscleMario: DAYM
ragemaster999: react harder :rage:
TheNakedFlame: LUL
syrob2804: What did he write?
i4cc8a9morw8kfrh: wrap it up domer squadD
MuscleMario: I one told that to a Teachers Assistant ... good times
MonkaSupreme: mylNob
forkdb: Hello
MuscleMario: squadW
directrix13: @georgehotz Learn functional language Elm instead of React since react was literally based on how Elm works
euranymous: I am groot
i4cc8a9morw8kfrh: so bad squadR
quevlo: Anyone have suggestions for how to learn programming? Want to become a Software developer or start off in database for experience. I have zero experience in coding btw
forkdb: Please talk something interesting
Ralph_124C_41: lol
Ziv0: LUL
residentsleeperrrrrrrrr: xqcSkip xqcSkip
Ricoello: mylBrain
MuscleMario: Elm is a web framework i thot
whichtom: @quevlo my dude there are a trillion resources online
whichtom: any website that teaches through practice
euranymous: I am groot
forkdb: Hello
Vinndy: ewww front-end boring stuff
MrOtotheP: we frontend developers now?
syrob2804: vue js
forkdb: What is not boring?!
rektiw0w: react isnt that boring even tho its front end
YouPowerRush: 123 go
MuscleMario: Okay, well anyone else here know about Wasm and its future goal?
hoffs: thats jquery
i4cc8a9morw8kfrh: lul
MrOtotheP: ClojureScript <3
zeroeagle1: why not try web assembly?
nautzz: yes they do actually, its called vanillajs
kyyllu: Only angular makes front end not boring
reyy911: @rektiw0w it is boring. Even
fear_ep: do you suggest to do AI as master degree? @georgehotz
Ralph_124C_41: hahahaha, right wing javascript
Hypheus_: LUL
XeroKool: lol
reyy911: @georgehotz said it
TheNakedFlame: Use svelte js 4Head
rektiw0w: @reyy911 why?
Zasuslive: Thoughts on John carmack saying his focus for the future is AGI?
forkdb: Please stay away from front end... you are gonna not like
directrix13: Conservative JavaScript framework is thoughtsandprayers.js
Ziv0: svelte LUL
LaheyFPS: Tim cook LUL
mdrake_: did they fix the keyboard
MuscleMario: I am stuck between Thinkpad X1 Extreme Gen 2 vs MBP 16
forkdb: And.........
Zasuslive: Thoughts on John carmack saying his focus for the future is AGI?
serhejenos: LUL LUL LUL LUL LUL
MonkaSupreme: you also need nvm so you can switch between node versions mylBrain
0xF61: Does it have esc ? @georgehotz
Vinndy: i feel like the problem is not learning React is what type of shit project do you even come up with to learn it
forkdb: What.............
Ralph_124C_41: @Zasuslive he's well off enough that he's just doing whatever he wants without an interest in growth
TheNakedFlame: PogChamp
MuscleMario: WASM bytecode compiler
MonkaSupreme: build twitch chat
Jadess: HSWP
Caene: Literally any project in react will automatically be shit.
MuscleMario: :D
vmarkushin: facebook
rektiw0w: twitch sudoku
reyy911: Todo app
Ricoello: just copy anything open source
reyy911: LUL
directrix13: chess
MuscleMario: websockets ttoo
Zabak378: Calculator
GGGrimmy: Make a new web framework in the react framework. Javascript folks love the layers.
LaheyFPS: build chat PogChamp
zeroeagle1: a front end for the twitchcoq
TheNakedFlame: PogChamp That's us
forkdb: Please do not touch frontend.. stick to back end only
crazywulf770: a scam ps4 emulator website in react
ragemaster999: twitch shat
Caene: LUL
MuscleMario: LOL
nautzz: PogChamp
revolutionist123: girlfriend finder
forkdb: Omg.....
i4cc8a9morw8kfrh: #ad
Ralph_124C_41: pay 20k and learn to be a professional front-end developer PogChamp
zeroeagle1: check the pricing
Zasuslive: @ralph_124c_41 yeah i doubt his objective is to increase his wealth, but I think he wants to leave something of significance behind
syrob2804: Do u live in bay area?
mdrake_: become a developer
MuscleMario: Just saw San Francisco for the first time last week, got back yesterday. Had a great time at a convention.
abk467: hey you could work at facebook Kappa
nautzz: george studying the ways of the grift
kyyllu: dude learn angular instead wtf
Vinndy: just pay 20k to learn CSS 4Head
Scott_w_c: what are your internet speeds
euranymous: linux for president
MuscleMario: rip
mdrake_: LUL
Scott_w_c: RIP
Zabak378: rip
LaheyFPS: ookla
XeroKool: LUL
i4cc8a9morw8kfrh: F
Hypheus_: F LUL
TheNakedFlame: LUL
directrix13: Make sure you put it in a Docker container using a Debian base orchestrated by Kubernetes
Ralph_124C_41: @Zasuslive yeah, I mean I wasn't criticizing, he's putting his skills to good use in whatever interests him at any given time
Vinndy: ???????
i4cc8a9morw8kfrh: OMEGALUL
MuscleMario: 3 fast
filipeoliveiraa: f
MonkaSupreme: well
Vinndy: LUL
forkdb: Dude .. you are trolling...
eax_ebx: f
MuscleMario: f
myasovlavashe: f
Larsson93: Saved
nautzz: speedtest brought the stream down for a sec i think lmao
MonkaSupreme: its so fast that it kills your stream
abk467: whew. that was a close call
ragemaster999: Jebaited
okeeeeeee: i have 46 LUL
UniversalGeneve: codecademy is usually good enough for me, i learned how to program in java, JS, and C# in a week.
Ziv0: dem dropped frames
pogu: I hate all of the crazy tags adg-asdf-important-component-tag in angular. React is way cleaner
LiIDrunk: thoughts on MBP 16
whichtom: holy shit what is happening
forkdb: He is trolling........
MonkaSupreme: I know your ip now, starts with 192 Kappa
MuscleMario: close the bitcoin miner
smurfd0: what did you think of the new macbook pro 16inch?
Scott_w_c: stream frozen LOL
Shasan_: i went to college to learn lisp now i am unemployed
whichtom: actually powerpoint
MonkaSupreme: leak leak
Santiago_LHC: Fast frame rates are overrated
UniversalGeneve: cyber police
kyyllu: why tf is he learning react?
Vinndy: hey george can i intern at comma
zeroeagle1: use vue instead
forkdb: Why don’t you come work for me:)
ragemaster999: just abort it 4Head
Caene: "Shopping list", oh dear God.
MuscleMario: Lisp is cool
komocode_: lolregex
hoffs: @kyyllu because he wants to work in a startup
komocode_: would you use regex to validate email?
Scott_w_c: sold your IP on ebay to elon musk he about to ddos you from starlink as a world wide test
kyyllu: dude learn angular then
ManWithNoFace: thoughts on the 16" mbp???
kyyllu: way better than react
Zasuslive: @ralph_124c_41 Yeah definitely, I wanted to basically know what George thought of the chances of him actually succeeding, considering he pretty much does in any field he enters
syrob2804: What salary are u expecting?
fwef64: This channel is going downhill.
s0rrz: "how to build a startup in a day"
Santiago_LHC: #memes
rektiw0w: worse...
MonkaSupreme: install nvm for nodehttp://dev.topheman.com/install-nvm-with-homebrew-to-use-multiple-versions-of-node-and-iojs-easily/
forkdb: Bad idea...
MuscleMario: damn geohot, do u go to ctf's or conference anymore?
reyy911: Angular is better imo
directrix13: @georgehotz write a distributed speed test app that can't be cheated by collusion with ISPs
UniversalGeneve: @georgehotz in terms of working at a slef diving company/ A.I. oriented product company, what would you say are "employable skills"?
razr22: angular is like react
nautzz: its just a meme dont get heated @kyyllu
Santiago_LHC: Angular is the 2015's React
komocode_: eLeCtRon
Sarcazeem: maybe flutter LUL
Caene: In how many languages does a person have to learn to make a shopping list, before he can call himself a dev? LUL
pogu: everythingisaplatformnow.jpg
reyy911: Check out RxJS.
xEHLE_: @MuscleMario he went to twitchcon, he is a streamer now
MuscleMario: LOL
reyy911: React is a mess.
zeroeagle1: go eith blazor
thegamer12349876: reactJS
MuscleMario: thoughts on mbp16
kyyllu: Angular is waaaaaaay better than react
MuscleMario: leggo
ManWithNoFace: yes
syrob2804: Socket io chat
Santiago_LHC: Let's buy macs
rektiw0w: new mac PogChamp
reyy911: Reminds me of php lmao
VLEESBROODTV: 16 inch 8 tb macbook lets go
MuscleMario: Im afraid of becomming a mac ecosystem guy.
forkdb: YES
euranymous: Build a PC instead
okeeeeeee: i like the old macs much better
GGGrimmy: Buy a dell and put linux on it
fwef64: What happened to your windows computer?
komocode_: butterfly keyboard is awesome
Santiago_LHC: #butterfly
MuscleMario: I just want my damn ESCAPE physical key
myasovlavashe: DansGame
bergsdal: apple bad
reyy911: Yes new mac
komocode_: better than scissors
jstoast: what mac do you have rn?
pogu: noooo
i4cc8a9morw8kfrh: these prices man wtf
forkdb: OHHHHHHHH
okeeeeeee: touch pad keyboard DansGame
Miu_OS: why not hackintosh?
rektiw0w: physical escape key PogChamp
MuscleMario: Physical Escape Key
xEHLE_: get the 6k macbook PogChamp
euranymous: I like the product but the price straight up repels me
LaheyFPS: AMD LUL
pogu: me too, I like Bfly v2
Santiago_LHC: It is big
Scott_w_c: i hae 13 inch and it is great
MuscleMario: I was going to get the Thinkpad X1 Extreme Gen2 , but then this ish came out.
ragemaster999: 4k pc PogChamp
komocode_: vue.js
Annex_Greenland: 4k for a macbook
ManWithNoFace: 16 is way too big
Vinndy: just $4k 4Head
Caene: 13 inch are perfect, I usually dock my shit when I come home anyway.
LiIDrunk: only 0.7" bigger
forkdb: ITS HUGE
whichtom: how portable even is 16 inch
euranymous: Just build a god damn PC instead of wasting money on expensive social media machine
whichtom: ye 13 inch is great
MuscleMario: Websockets
UniversalGeneve: high T
Ziv0: I have the 16in one and it is kinda big
syrob2804: Socket IO @georgehotz
forkdb: BUILD SLACK
Annex_Greenland: 16 inch laptop LULW
Zabak378: 6 inches are also fine
FargioFarmani: i like my 13 inches too
Santiago_LHC: inch jokes incoming
Scott_w_c: plz apple i want 26 inch in my backpack i need moniter at school
i4cc8a9morw8kfrh: @euranymous imagine paying 3k for a laptop
Shasan_: use laravel with react
MonkaSupreme: install nvm instead, less headache
reyy911: I have a 15”
swagettiyolonaise69: that's what she said
ragemaster999: @georgehotz web sockets
MuscleMario: I'm using Brave right now, anyone else?
ImNotTrolling: socket io and node js
thegamer12349876: use yarn better than npm
MonkaSupreme: yarn LUL
Vinndy: lol i'm just writing a bittorrent client in node js
euranymous: @i4cc8a9morw8kfrh I better buy a i9 and an rtx 2080 ti with that just to upgrade my existing PC
directrix13: you should get a unicomp model m keyboard. It's a lot like your butterfly keyboard in many ways.
pogu: Firefox all way
okeeeeeee: ejabbered server?
kyyllu: @georgehotz learn django xd
zeroeagle1: yarn > npm
Scott_w_c: use HTML
VidaSabudabu: use graphQL on AWS with DynamoDB
yuptheladsdownthecans: @LeadCoder STOP sending the same thing over and over idiot
Annex_Greenland: coolest chat app LUL
i4cc8a9morw8kfrh: @euranymous true
ytazn: i just won a 5k
whichtom: LUL
Santiago_LHC: BOOM
okeeeeeee: LUL
XeroKool: LUL
i4cc8a9morw8kfrh: LOOOOOOOOOL
UniversalGeneve: LUL
Lefer_: LUL
Ralph_124C_41: LUL
Zabak378: OMEGALUL
AlcaponeYou: LUL
okeeeeeee: savage LUL
Rtc_ti5: hahahaha
Shasan_: LUL
Scott_w_c: BloodTrail
kyyllu: LUL
LaheyFPS: not subbed LUL
rektiw0w: oof
Keyeh: good morning @georgehotz
directrix13: lol
reyy911: LUL LUL LUL
speeddrawing101: Nice
forkdb: WTF
MonkaSupreme: mylNob
FlySociety2o9: LUL
notoroszbig: grpc?
Annex_Greenland: excessive
ManWithNoFace: F
ytazn: hey no offense but you look great
Santiago_LHC: You know when your username is "LeadCoder", you made it.
forkdb: ifeelbadfortneperson
Caene: @LeadCoder Better subscribe to come back. LUL
erichtp: LUL
Vinndy: you will have to "emulate" discovery by having the server be the middle man all the time
revolutionist123: f
MonkaSupreme: p2p
Scott_w_c: and sell it to stream lab and buy that macbook!
i4cc8a9morw8kfrh: comedyStare
Keyeh: 🤔
sultantw: ex leader now
reyy911: @annex_greenland you thinks so? You should get banned too
MuscleMario: inb4 this a botnet
okeeeeeee: try erlang @georgehotz
hoffs: just use a blokchain
pogu: 1, YES PLEASE
LaheyFPS: and then you dos us all
directrix13: you are going to need some nat traversal
MonkaSupreme: write in solidity Kappa
speeddrawing101: Do you know React? @georgehotz
mariusmafius: erlang DansGame elixir SeemsGood
kektobiologist: can u add in title what you're making? @georgehotz
ytazn: hey great idea
MuscleMario: elixir <- will be fun
VidaSabudabu: learn graphQL and use from Reactjs
Keyeh: eggs and sausage Kreygasm
MuscleMario: ill go make breakfast too
erlsek: what is he doing now?
Santiago_LHC: FUN
LaheyFPS: egg burrito PogChamp
Caene: Time for brekkie
dorkmo: https://github.com/cabal-club
euranymous: Lets make some chicken tendies
forkdb: Shall I sub ...
reyy911: Frozen food otw
zeroeagle1: is their ui stuff for elixir?
directrix13: breakfast.js
UniversalGeneve: bacon, eggs, sausage and hashbrowns
FlySociety2o9: sandwhich LUL
dorkmo: @georgehotz ^
Shasan_: george a genius it would take me a year to build that
ytazn: chat app
ytazn: @erlsek
erlsek: nice
Jewishrambo: 🙄
Keyeh: Discord slayer PogChamp i'm ready
ytazn: guys
LaheyFPS: DansGame dirty
ytazn: boys
pogu: @Shasan_ doubt it, it'll take a less resourceful person a few weeks at most
12ka4: hey dude can you teach us vim? your vim skills are lit.
ytazn: i will also make eggs now
Vinndy: play you were the shit in high school it's sick
LaheyFPS: Beethoven
VLEESBROODTV: cabal looks hot
directrix13: directrix13 subscribed at Tier 1.
Annex_Greenland: LUL
cjocol2201: hi
swagettiyolonaise69: dont forget to add a ban function
LaheyFPS: LUL
XeroKool: LUL
kyyllu: LOL
god_damn: get that guy outta here
FlySociety2o9: LUL
Keyeh: xcalBanhammer
ytazn: i hate fun
pogu: 🍌
forkdb: Play your rapp song
Annex_Greenland: whys he so awnry
ManWithNoFace: what chair is that
pogu: lul slow internet
hoffs: herman miller
euranymous: play some tomcr00se
Keyeh: arab subtitles though
Fundlak: turkish*
pogu: I love this already, fml
Keyeh: @Fundlak ty
ManWithNoFace: thanks hoffs
i4cc8a9morw8kfrh: @Keyeh are you serious
directrix13: somebody let the dog in with mud on his foot
Keyeh: @i4cc8a9morw8kfrh no, just clueless
Keyeh: i mean, yes
i4cc8a9morw8kfrh: squadD
i4cc8a9morw8kfrh: comedyStare
Santiago_LHC: Breakfast stream
st47ik: cant hear you from that far
residentsleeperrrrrrrrr: "comedy"
kyyllu: @georgehotz make the chat app with Django instead of shitty js
byte_baron: what a swaggalicious song
khilshot: Yo yo geohot
byte_baron: it's so hip!
i4cc8a9morw8kfrh: @kyyllu that would be great
byte_baron: so... so... utterly shit
euranymous: Do you guys get disappointed by absurd contribution of apple fanboys to the monopoly?
XnitronQ: PogChamp
Vinndy: PogChamp
okeeeeeee: tomcr00se PogChamp
Santiago_LHC: what monopoly
kytos1k: PogChamp
st47ik: PogChamp
swami_ramdev_baba: oh geo
FlySociety2o9: PogChamp
ytazn: i put bacon in my eggs
euranymous: @Santiago_LHC Literally every housewife wants an iphone
okeeeeeee: rip pc
ytazn: not to be mean @georgehotz but you are the best builder ever
TheNakedFlame: monkaS I C U
Santiago_LHC: @euranymous Where I live only like 10% of all people have iPhones
komocode_: what's your dj name? Hotz dropping the 🔥
mkdrmnd: @euranymous so you're asking if anyone else is annoyed that people like to buy the products they like?
dorkmo: https://github.com/cabal-club
MonkaSupreme: I bet you gonna have some trouble with P2P stuff in the browser
swami_ramdev_baba: oh geoz how do you just live all hours by only typing or leanring
st47ik: whats on the plate Kappa
SmokeSomethin: what man, hows your day going?
okeeeeeee: LUL
god_damn: 🤕
speeddrawing101: YEs
euranymous: @mkdrmnd I dont mean that. I meant the company is selling an inferior product for absurd prices which happens to be a status symbol
Santiago_LHC: #obstacles
gator____: wonder if George has Headspace premium LUL
razr22: play at 2x
st47ik: ╰(*°▽°*)╯
razr22: jony ive LUL
Santiago_LHC: @euranymous I think you don't understand what a monopoly is
god_damn: LMFAOOO
swami_ramdev_baba: I daily learn like this but i do 5 to 6 mastrub** i cant control it,
Santiago_LHC: #curious
swami_ramdev_baba: How to control it guy
Santiago_LHC: #neural
Caene: LUL
st47ik: neural networks PogChamp
FlySociety2o9: What is this?
god_damn: 🤨 mind wondering...
st47ik: he's optimizing his neural networks
mkdrmnd: @euranymous the iPhone is only a status symbol to poor people, and also, 'inferior product' is a poor assessment because you haven't considered their perspective and how iOS might make it superior for them...
Keyeh: that's some "deep" meditation
swami_ramdev_baba: Also @georgehotz , do you know onehack.us website and what it is giving to world
jrrbls: have you tried the Sam Harris one
FlySociety2o9: training the neural network
god_damn: he really is vibing
ytazn: have u tried vue?
FargioFarmani: this is hilarious
Santiago_LHC: We are meditating bros
ytazn: i think if i started over i might not use framework
st47ik: oh yeah
swami_ramdev_baba: Who is working onehack.us is that you
jellyjar: ah meditating, thought we were getting brainwashed
FlySociety2o9: I'm ready
kyyllu: Y O G A B O Y Z
gator____: breathe through the root chakra, chat
mariusmafius: u gotta do this shiet before touching any web framework
FargioFarmani: cant do react without mediating first
st47ik: ^
Santiago_LHC: :breathe:
FlySociety2o9: ^
god_damn: 🤨
leopp: @mariusmafius LMFAO
pogu: lol headspace is such a shit product. I like for starting out, wouldn't say premium is worth it
swami_ramdev_baba: how to control mastrub*
Santiago_LHC: https://www.calm.com/
ytazn: i like to hold a weapon while i think it makes me feel a bit better
st47ik: D E E P
suteki1: 😐
kyyllu: @ytazn MonkaS
swami_ramdev_baba: i am addicted to that like john don
nesbyy1: What we doing now?
st47ik: NotLikeThis
god_damn: @nesbyy1 vibing bro
swagettiyolonaise69: not sure
ytazn: @kyyllu it's weird but try it
Santiago_LHC: We are meditating
FlySociety2o9: monkaS
xohadi: vibe check
st47ik: bruh moment
Thobrik: okay who called the police
hoffs: woop woop 🚓
st47ik: Kappa
god_damn: feds monkaS
leopp: *sirens in the distance
Unsavable: Sirens amplifying the relaxation.
LaheyFPS: haha sirens
suteki1: CiGrip
swami_ramdev_baba: OM NAMAH SHIYAY
rektiw0w: lmao wtf is this
stale2000: monkaS
kyyllu: imagine meditating before using react LUL
jellyjar: namaste
notoroszbig: namaste
FlySociety2o9: !keyboard
YouPowerRush: 123 go
st47ik: @kyyllu that's the point LUL
Santiago_LHC: meditation is the only way to use react
cjocol2201: monkaS
Azermite: Meditation is pointless ?
aa_ato: Sss
Pryetranka: murdaEmusk
swami_ramdev_baba: @georgehotz , ARE YOU INTROVERT AND EXTROVERT
VLEESBROODTV: zzzzzz
kyyllu: react is shit why nobody told him
gator____: @Azermite not entirely. It's supposed to increase gray matter in the brain
hoffs: @Azermite nah bro, its only way to unlocking 99% of your brian
ytazn: i dont use any of the redux stuff it's too complicated
YouPowerRush: sleepy boii
suteki1: FeelsGoodMan 🚬 ﱞﱞﱞﱞﱞﱞﱞﱞﱞﱞﱞﱞﱞﱞﱞﱞﱞﱞﱞﱞﱞﱞﱞﱞﱞﱞﱞﱞﱞﱞﱞﱞﱞﱞﱞ
Caene: I feel so calm.. I feel like a shoe.
XeroKool: This is stressing me out
Santiago_LHC: a bit of space
stale2000: MrDestructoid
st47ik: vue is calmer than react 4Head
Azermite: Angular : yes
swami_ramdev_baba: @georgehotz , tell me how to stop having mastrub***, when i am alone i cant control it
Santiago_LHC: #nojudgement
nesbyy1: Can someone link the video please
thebastl: @georgehotz Do you think making open pilot work for e-scooters is the next big thing?
nesbyy1: the video of the orator
nesbyy1: or whatever its called
gmx27: @realrajanpaudel try stoicism
VLEESBROODTV: its headspace
kyyllu: Just use django dude forget about react
god_damn: george really about it
st47ik: Kreygasm
stale2000: Never did I thought to see the day of Programming ASMR
FargioFarmani: its an app
YouPowerRush: sikk headspace bruh
pogu: I feel like a blob controlling my body
ytazn: i meditate too but maybe not for as long
gator____: I hear in silicon valley you have to do this before every HR meeting
thebastl: @kyyllu Heretic!
Santiago_LHC: #breathing
EnjoyToLive: are you scared of leadcoder
st47ik: @kyyllu django for frontend WutFace
thebastl: Did he just fart?
gator____: yes
kyyllu: Not for the front end, but for building the app
suteki1: yes
VLEESBROODTV: eggs are cold by now
aa_ato: this work!
pogu: @gator____ yeah, HR is so annoying that before and after purge of memory and emotion is necessary
Santiago_LHC: #chill
kyyllu: Also, Angular for front end is way better than react
Keyeh: > "preferred text editor" > not vim LUL
gator____: LUL
ytazn: i guess it is the start of the project tho
EnjoyToLive: chill
thebastl: Is he aware that the stream is running?
gator____: no
st47ik: @thebastl yeah
Santiago_LHC: He is aware of nothing but thyself
ytazn: hey you got this geohot u r the best one
st47ik: LUL
EnjoyToLive: you don't have the balls to challenge the Robed guy
st47ik: jailbreaking the brain
Santiago_LHC: Can someone ban this wannabe hacker?
kyyllu: No effort required
god_damn: this is how man reaches his apex
hoffs: george about to bust one
swami_ramdev_baba: @georgehotz , say ohmmmmmmm
st47ik: DansGame
lwasd: Hey George!
leopp: he's channeling his JS BEAST MODE
MrBlackPanther: !keyboard
LaheyFPS: scream in the mic when done :)
jellyjar: we are about to witness some next level coding when hes done
lwasd: Just created a security tool for NPM that helps developers safely consume OSS, interested?
st47ik: Setup Option 1: Write Code in the Browser 4Head
ytazn: i am an asynchronous process
ytazn: i will wait patiently while the thread does other things
Santiago_LHC: #pleasantthoughts
zoki_macola: is he ok
lwasd: wtf...
Pryetranka: no
ragemaster999: this might be the best javascript code a man has ever written
kyyllu: Self driving cars built using react lets go
EnjoyToLive: he's just scared @zoki_macola
ytazn: i will be executed by a browser
aa_ato: DeadMan
lwasd: https://trustd.dev ?
gator____: can you imagine george in an ayahuasca ceremony LUL
st47ik: u need to meditate before using react SMOrc
xrealyy: he should do this before the stream
zoki_macola: he looks anxious
kyyllu: selfdriving.js
st47ik: LUL
martinkirilov: Did you get the new MB @georgehotz ? Finally a physical escape key for proper vim using
Santiago_LHC: "let the mind do whatever it wants"
bayed222: Cheer100
lwasd: Anyone here use Node.js?
lwasd: Or NPM?
xrealyy: "boobs"
aPosterior: he calling kylo ren?
pogu: @martinkirilov Switch esc and caps. How do you even use the normal escape key with vim
st47ik: @lwasd most do
hoffs: @lwasd stop shilling your shity
lwasd: Mean :(
kyyllu: @lwasd I do
gator____: cyber bully
martinkirilov: @pogu no caps on HHKB :(
lwasd: It ain't shitty.
st47ik: smells DansGame
Santiago_LHC: appreciate boys
Zabak378: What do you guys think about PHP?
leopp: I use CTRL [ to exit insert mode
lwasd: I just build a free dev tool to help educate developers on vulnerable OSS packages as they install them.
st47ik: smells like eggs in there
jrrbls: have u tried Sam Harris one
lwasd: I tryna help the world :( :(
ragemaster999: he is about to concatenate different types in javascript
Pryetranka: ResidentSleeper
pogu: @martinkirilov I just looked it up rofl
MonkaSupreme: good group session
oksan309: Has a fly ever wandered into ur mouth while riding a bicycle LUL
gator____: swalloed a beetle once ^
lwasd: @kyyllu Wooooo.
gator____: swallowed*
Santiago_LHC: #missingtheopportunity
st47ik: @lwasd npm does that kinda?
kyyllu: @lwasd work more with python tho
ragemaster999: he is rewiring on live stream PogChamp
ytazn: geohot is the embodiment of low coupling
PhysoTronic: what app is he using?
bayed222: headspace
mlgdotca: why is he learning react
Santiago_LHC: #engage #experience #reflect
leopp: he is reading the chat
st47ik: PogChamp
ytazn: at his core geohot is maintainable code
lwasd: @st47ik @kyyllu NPM does, other package managers don't - Python is next.
balzak43: is this the new ` import zen` >
LiIDrunk: wtf i thought doing weed was the correct way
MonkaSupreme: be careful with streaming headspace content on twitch. @georgehotz
lwasd: And we also do licence control as well.
lwasd: AGPL etc.
Vjasal: have you ever tried hypnosis?
martinkirilov: tell me you're eating fruit looms or I'll be disappointed
hoffs: ok sensei what is your zen level and how is your chakra doing
LaheyFPS: please im too relaxed, scream into the microphone. :)
aa_ato: 😂😂😂😂
byte_baron: @Vjasal isn't that an illegal wrestling move or something?
smurfd0: i geuss the meditation helps?
aa_ato: 😂😂😂😂😂😂😂
leopp: the eggs are cold?
gator____: @byte_baron you're thinking of the stone cold stunna LUL
st47ik: so calm Kreygasm
lwasd: Try the tool and let me know your thoughts?
swagettiyolonaise69: meditation is not for thinking
st47ik: @georgehotz signaling servers?
ytazn: in front of our eyes geohot has ascended to the level of the best developer in the world
lwasd: @st47ik you legend.
martinkirilov: yarn is so much better for react
khilshot: Wanna give VScode a try?
MonkaSupreme: we need a tracker
st47ik: @lwasd wat
PhysoTronic: perfect for "simple" skill sunday LUL
ragemaster999: are you ready to concatenate different types in javascript? @georgehotz
lwasd: Question is, which is safer?
Santiago_LHC: @khilshot He already has
st47ik: lookup signalhub George
thebastl: @georgehotz Do you own a boosted board?
dorkmo: did george look at cabal yet lol
khilshot: Most of the time i see him using vim.
xrealyy: slow net huh
two_eight: take a look at svelte. its react without the bullshit
ytazn: geohot is simple architecture
PhysoTronic: georgehotz what is your background? first time here. are you coming from JS or you usually work in other languages
Santiago_LHC: @khilshot He codes on vim, but uses vs code to read code
Thobrik: George started speaking with that cute yoga teacher voice like the headspace guy
LiIDrunk: lol still installing
ckrpasa: finally watching you alive and you are making meditation! LOL
LiIDrunk: brew is trash
st47ik: @georgehotz u goona use webrtc?
thebastl: @georgehotz Do you play video games?
swami_ramdev_baba: I love windows , hate mac
Santiago_LHC: nobody "loves" Windows
minichota: I love Linux, hate mac
st47ik: there are a few p2p webrtc projects
dorkmo: https://github.com/beakerbrowser/beaker
MonkaSupreme: maybe give peerjs a try
st47ik: u need a signaling server to connect peers tho
swami_ramdev_baba: windows is best friend for poor peoples
khilshot: Socketio is good for chat apps.
dorkmo: basically all use dht i think
Serbius: hello geo when will you make a new rap song, i need more gym pump up songs
Santiago_LHC: @swami_ramdev_baba lol, you say that as if it was free
swami_ramdev_baba: haha
swami_ramdev_baba: it is free , i use cracked version
swami_ramdev_baba: all is carcket
cursedelboom0: !keyboard
pogu: @Serbius It's super weird but I actually work out better with brain.fm light focus than the standard gym pump up songs
Santiago_LHC: Try linux, it's actually free.
mariusmafius: monkaS
st47ik: https://socket.io/blog/socket-io-p2p/ uses WebRTC
swami_ramdev_baba: *cracked
PhysoTronic: georgehotz first time here.. are you coming from JS or you usually work in other languages
leopp: hey @georgehotz, try gg=G in vim
jay_al97: you're doing javascript today
Serbius: @pogu im not kidding i worked out with geos songs
kyyllu: @physotronic usually he uses python
pogu: That's indent all lines in VIM
leopp: gg=G idents the code for you automatically
pogu: gg=G is indent all lines
Vinndy: front end development on vim might be a little bit of a stretch isn't it
TheBigK02: hi
FargioFarmani: In normal mode, typing gg=G will reindent the entire file.
ytazn: geohot has already reached godlike architectural ability and will write highly consistent codes
TheBigK02: twitch is so buggy... wanted to watch a vod... only for subs... then i subbed... still cant watch... what is this shit
jellyjar: is your current one 16gb?
dorkmo: new maccc booook
w9cceixh24b23ouiljlhmyp1: only 32GB ram, i see youre only going to install one dependecy then? Kappa
PhysoTronic: kyyllu does he have some project that he works on or he creates new ones often?
kyyllu: python > js
khilshot: Do you hate java?
swami_ramdev_baba: @georgehotz ,, how do you control yourself from mastrubation , give me detailed tips, i am addicted to that shit. I am out,
Neeuuro: 50 tabs open in 10 different windows =D
kyyllu: xd
MuscleMario: English muffins, egg, salami, meunster cheese, yeet.
ytazn: geohot is the grittiest builder in the world
jay_al97: why are you learning react?
TheBigK02: @georgehotz ... step 1: hack twitch step2: fix twitch step3: get 1 milion subs on instagram... deal?
PhysoTronic: Neeuuro i have currently ~900 tabs
mlgdotca: why vim
Santiago_LHC: 95% of chat is "The thing I like is the best thing, unlike that other thing. Why aren't you using my thing?"
TheBigK02: why not vim
ytazn: LUL
kyyllu: @physotronic you mean in general or in js?
forkdb: Vim teach me
maxjowett: react LUL
pogu: @Santiago_LHC That's most of the conversation on the planet lul
swami_ramdev_baba: @georgehotz , how to increase my neurons and be genius
PhysoTronic: kyyllu well in general and in js. does he wants to learn JS so he made skill sunday?
ManWithNoFace: OnClick
rektiw0w: u have to do camelcase for onclick @georgehotz
Santiago_LHC: @pogu Depends who you hang up with
st47ik: @georgehotz u know about IPFS?
Lutefisk123: onclick with big C
ytazn: build for fun implies cream of the crop
chocblade: Can you say me a marked for exploits ?
kyyllu: @physotronic he is a famous hacker and runs a self driving cars startup if thats what u mean
MuscleMario: Did you know that bitwise ops on a JS var forces it to an INT rather than a float which increases performance when number crunching?
pogu: @Santiago_LHC I mean even if you say a statement, you're essentially saying "Im thinking in this way, I'm saying this so you can thing in this way too"
swami_ramdev_baba: Bye @georgehotz brother , i am interested in deep learning and going to learn come to you in later
kyyllu: @physotronic he is learning js because he is making a "simple skill sunday"
PhysoTronic: kyyllu didnt know that. does he ever demonstrate how to actually hack something?
Vinndy: this doesn't exist on that context, callbacks are supposed to be "pure"
Spidey2711: hat is some piss poor logic @pogu
restitutione: e =>
rektiw0w: remove the curly braces
kingkong3211: use back ticks with dollar sign in front of opening curly bracket
kyyllu: @physotronic yes, actually he is pretty famous, if u do a search on Google you will know more about his story
ytazn: this is probably dumb but i dont use classes in react
anthraxvirus322: what are we doing today chat
mariusmafius: pussy
kyyllu: @physotronic I think there are some of these hacking videos in yt
martinkirilov: what are you reacting to? Kappa
pogu: Watch hs Lex Friedman podcast
pogu: his*
ytazn: @anthraxvirus322 chat app in react
MuscleMario: backticks are string templates in new JS
two_eight: gotta love that all the react tutorials now use the outdated class syntax. every 2 months you should be ready to learn new syntax :)
MuscleMario: allow $ in strings
khilshot: this context is different inside arrow function.
anthraxvirus322: @ytazn thanks kind sir SeemsGood
skynetrobot: is there a moderator in here that works for Facebook, I get timed out for mentioning lit-html ??
martinkirilov: @MuscleMario template literals, I'm surprised I still remember the name, haven't used js in a while
ytazn: no offense to boomers but i dont understand why they care so much about object orientation
johnny_thehobo: took me 4 months to barely understand react and geo is out here doing it in ~2 hours
Quad___lol: use functional react JS DansGame no one has time to type redundant shit
maxjowett: these tutorials are old bloated es5 examples
st47ik: https://github.com/Codaisseur/react-p2p-chat LUL
715209: you don't really need the constructor
LaheyFPS: monkaS
MuscleMario: Moderate your way into Partner
Quad___lol: https://www.robinwieruch.de/react-function-component
pogu: @st47ik 👏
martinkirilov: ``"backtick"$ string here"backtick"
two_eight: look at the new react hooks syntax
rektiw0w: the tutorial is fine
onewithoutnamee: onewithoutnamee subscribed with Twitch Prime.
MuscleMario: everything has been done, just the question is, how well. lol
khilshot: try scrimba
Pryetranka: react hooks is way to go
khilshot: it's free
forkdb: I think he likes to ban viewers...
PhysoTronic: kyyllu damn, he is real deal. just read few bits on wiki
ytazn: does anyone here know how to get the html from a site and print it out outside the browser?
Santiago_LHC: @forkdb Mostly trolls or people who are dumb and way off topic
ytazn: dude yes youre a genius
Arksam: monkaS
Vinndy: @ytazn use curl
electriclime: You could probably pass  objects as a parameter to the anonymous function then use it in the alert
pogu: VoteYea
jay_al97: lol
reaganchisholm: the big idea
MonkaSupreme: 10v10 tic tac toe
champ900: try alt F4
MuscleMario: biggest
forkdb: @santiago_lhc I know, was just kidding... I like him...an inspiration
frediiiez: PogChamp
printhellosailor: I literally just implemented a server-side webrtc peer data connection a few hours ago
SpanglishGamer: Lol wow
SpanglishGamer: Genius
ytazn: @Vinndy ty
revolutionist123: PogChamp
BatkoTheBat: wow
st47ik: Also this distributed p2p chat app runs on IPFS https://github.com/orbitdb/orbit - https://orbit.chat/
SpanglishGamer: w0otahHigh
printhellosailor: implementing a server-side webrtc peer connection with a data channel is the only way to get a UDP connection to browsers right now
dorkmo: twitch connect 4 plz
skynetrobot: lit-html
two_eight: wouldn't websockets be better for tictactoe
st47ik: PogChamp
MuscleMario: ouch
electriclime: PeerJS is a simple wrapper for WebRTC that makes it very easy. Basically works like socketio
johnny_thehobo: implement some kind of ticket system so people have to pay to play vs you
khilshot: try scrimba (react tutorial)
forkdb: I like you george
printhellosailor: websockets would be simpler, but not as much fun as UDP over webrtc
swagettiyolonaise69: theres no winner in tic tac toe if you're good enough
equalizer_____: Чувствую русских в чате
champ900: I like you George
directrix13: ipfs isn't 100% JavaScript though currently
Vinndy: but what's the source of truth in this type of services
forkdb: He,lobgundu
Serbius: Pog
MitMax: MitMax subscribed with Twitch Prime. They've subscribed for 2 months! HolidayPresent HolidayPresent HolidayPresent
forkdb: What is pig?
forkdb: Pog
Santiago_LHC: PogChamp
ytazn: when i curl "http://philadelphia.craigslist.org" @Vinndy nothing prints?
kektobiologist: @georgehotz can you take your mic out of your keyboard
Ziv0: setState
Quad___lol: use setState
ytazn: keyboard sounds great
Vinndy: @ytazn do curl -L <url>
ytazn: ty
forkdb: What keyboard is he usually using?
Santiago_LHC: HHKB2
st47ik: @forkdb forbidden question NotLikeThis
forkdb: Ohgg StoneLightning
leopp: we don't talk about the keyboard here
mariusmafius: ban inc
ytazn: @Vinndy u r genius
st47ik: LUL
rektiw0w: some people abt to get banned
okeeeeeee: do you know 2 level tictoctoe? just make another tictoctoe grid in each of the 9 squares. the opponent always has to put his cross inside the area where the other player set his cross. e.g. put circle on left side into right field, then opponent has to put a cross anywhere into to right big square one. @georgehotz
Vinndy: no keyboard talk here
forkdb: Ohgg￼
st47ik: react ResidentSleeper
okeeeeeee: goal is to win in any small square
Quad___lol: @georgehotz 27 setState
champ900: change handleClick = (i) =>
two_eight: REACT HOOKS
Serbius: i never thought i would lose nnn watching a guy code so smoothly Kappa
ytazn: setstate is async
kektobiologist: please use es6 saves a lot of boilerplate
Santiago_LHC: Here is what George's setup looks like: https://www.instagram.com/p/Bx0DMrUAxE-/
Vinndy: react: "we don't do mutation here"
W1lkins: people writing javascript on stream, whole chat becomes javascript experts
st47ik: @W1lkins cuz its the most popular LUL
Boethig: you dont mutate the state because the dom diff algorithm wont catch it
ytazn: never used .fill before what a god
kyyllu: @st47ik most popular and utterly shit
kyyllu: xd
st47ik: not really
kyyllu: jk
forkdb: @santiago_lhc Thank you very much
kyyllu: But I think python better
johnny_thehobo: hmm... yes. i understand
ytazn: it's cool u r learning it super fast
Quad___lol: called it 15mins ago jokerd6Weird
st47ik: @kyyllu rust is superior imo, just give it a few years
kyyllu: python ans js are my main ones
zoki_macola: dont call prop.onClick
kyyllu: @st47ik I was about to learn Go instead of Rust
zoki_macola: just pass function
dorkmo: woo
do_not_erase: lol
YouPowerRush: 123 go
Serbius: @georgehotz did you compete in programming in HS?
Nubadoxd: If it ain't the sexiest CEO on twitch shedGurt
jay_al97: could the terminal
st47ik: LUL
CaptCalifornia: the boomer is back online PepeLaugh
Nubadoxd: Hey George, how are you doing today?
0om4ar: hey man what do you think of golang ?
kektobiologist: not using vscode in 2019 FeelsWeirdMan
ytazn: this is quick and dirty
st47ik: Vanilla JS is better than React for this case LUL
kokokaik: aggressive typing
forkdb: @santiago_lhc Please accept my friend request on twitch
rektiw0w: they make it better as u progress through the tutorial
ytazn: sometimes u gotta do quick and dirty
fluzfluz: hi georgehotz
sirvapealots: @rektiw0w here, learn bad habits and fix it later Kappa
sirvapealots: @rektiw0w a bad habit will eat you alive
printhellosailor: react is not the best... but it's popular, and usable
forkdb: What is the meaning of noob
rektiw0w: @sirvapealots well yea...
foxubu: Is the title of the stream still valid?
rektiw0w: @sirvapealots however the point of it is to teach u of the basic concepts and not good practices
foxubu: Oh thanks
ytazn: the title is great
fwef64: deprecated is not pronounced like that
electriclime: PeerJS is a wrapper for WebRTC that makes it very simple to use.
sirvapealots: @rektiw0w learn the basics the worst ways possible Kappa
0om4ar: @kyyllu, golang is definitely the future
Pryetranka: LUL
estrangedHD: supported on chrome & opera, it's not like they use the same engine LUL
ytazn: yeah redux is way complicated i hate it
Nubadoxd: But ain't you a god amongst coders, you don't need to practice senpai Pepeflower
two_eight: webrtc doesn't work on firefox?
sirvapealots: @rektiw0w learn how to lift weights by using the worst forms possible, so you'll ruin your joints forever Kappa
kyyllu: @0om4ar yea I really like it
forkdb: Sing something george
Serbius: @georgehotz you should make it so it can select to random people in chat to play against each other
colanzio5: check out redux if you wanna refactor out state from components
ytazn: LUL
Vinndy: no
sirvapealots: @georgehotz @rektiw0w learn how to lift weights by using the worst forms possible, so you'll ruin your joints forever Kappa
kyyllu: @champ900 self driving cars in js lets go
jay_al97: the p2p gh repo was a troll
Nubadoxd: @georgehotz but ain't you a god amongst coders, you don't need to practice senpai Pepeflower
sirvapealots: @Nubadoxd he had to sign an agreement with Sony to stop hacking their playstations in the future LUL
YouPowerRush: 1 2 3 go
0om4ar: implement it from rfc 😡
sirvapealots: @Nubadoxd that's old news though :)
kyyllu: @nubadoxd he is doing this just to satisfy the lads
kyyllu: c:
Nubadoxd: @sirvapealots I know, LUL he's probably just bored
Vinndy: i spent the weekend learning node js and react but got kind of demotivated cause it's too many frameworks and they change all the time
sirvapealots: @Nubadoxd bored? nah, he seems to keep going :)
Nubadoxd: The simpletons in chat KEKW
directrix13: you just pin the files in IPFS, you don't really upload
kyyllu: @vinndy node and react wont go anywhere for a while dude, chill
sirvapealots: @Nubadoxd keeps on going with good ol' coding :)
Quad___lol: simpletons and singletons in chat jokerd6Kekmad
kratosboii: PogChamp
two_eight: Pog
forkdb: What is pog?
two_eight: PogU
anguscupcake: I'm a quadruple
sirvapealots: @forkdb Pog means Pog PogChamp
Nubadoxd: singletons... we're in George's chat, theirs only players here @quad___lol
0om4ar: add bbtv emote
Nubadoxd: PogChamp
sirvapealots: Loading........................
kratosboii: can someone explain to me whats going on
kyyllu: self resolving tic tac toe?
two_eight: copy past every medium article you find. modern web development PogChamp
TuleFTW: i feel better about myself knowing george hotz also copy pastes from medium articles
sirvapealots: Loading..............
ytazn: is ipfs better than heroku?
Quad___lol: heroku is better :]
kyyllu: tic tac toe startup incoming
directrix13: @georgehotz you want the ipns name so that it reflects changes going forward
sirvapealots: POGGERS
sirvapealots: WORKS LUL
Nubadoxd: It's the one their using tho shedLife
sirvapealots: P O G G E R S
Nubadoxd: KEKW
frediiiez: fetching /etc/passwd
razr22: LUL
kektobiologist: can someone copy stuff from his pc?
razr22: scanning file tree as we speak
1monkjuice: whats the difference with ngnix and this?
crazywulf770: maybe index.html works?
two_eight: p2p speed LUL
ytazn: if you fetch from your computer does your computer not need to always be on
ytazn: i have no idea
two_eight: build react
Nubadoxd: @georgehotz will you let the games begin? I feel that chats going to get bloody when the tic tac tow action begins DarkMode
sirvapealots: @georgehotz it has to be uploaded to IPFS i suppose
QED__: 5Head
directrix13: is your firewall blocking incoming connections
W1lkins: mac firewall Kappa
sirvapealots: @QED__ hey, hotz is a legend unlike some pleb streamers LUL
anguscupcake: @georgehotz favorite textbooks?
Nubadoxd: He's the man, the legend Geohotz
W1lkins: 50 Russian peers Kappa
sirvapealots: @georgehotz make your own repo Pog
kratosboii: @anguscupcake probably wikipedia
sirvapealots: @georgehotz likely your files haven't uploaded yet
kratosboii: lol
god_damn: i wish i had peers
mdrake_: i am peerless
rektiw0w: @god_damn me too
kratosboii: !keyboard
two_eight: HHKB
kratosboii: 5y
glitch3dout: Check the console
kratosboii: ty*
sirvapealots: @georgehotz try a video
Counteron: How is the app being built on the cloud?
YouPowerRush: 3 2 1 go
Counteron: exactly
sirvapealots: POGGERS
directrix13: @georgehotz you want to use the ipns name so that we can reference updated versions
directrix13: otherwise the hash updates with every new change
champ900: @georgehotz just use ngrok
sirvapealots: @champ900 so how is it better exactly?
sirvapealots: try opening it in a new tab
1monkjuice: looks like this is descentrilized in contrast to ngrok
directrix13: oooh private information reveal
two_eight: this is some pied piper shit
sirvapealots: @directrix13 public key :)
Serbius: so how does ipfs work?
directrix13: but it's just the directory in the current state
rektiw0w: ipfs looks cool
sirvapealots: @georgehotz post a link here so we can try it LUL
residentsleeperrrrrrrrr: lets hack some sony devices!!
georgehotz: https://ipfs.infura.io/ipfs/QmfWYwhPjzBHcdaN2bhwDYU8WuDHBZhvwQUCQvBokUu8JK
1monkjuice: ddos incoming
empathiie: nothing happens
gonzaloquintas: isnt loading
sirvapealots: not loading LUL
unique_ptr_: dont work boi
razr22: LUL
directrix13: that gateway is ass
yaus_baus: uptime?
two_eight: need MORE seeders
sirvapealots: @two_eight need more seeders Kappa
dorkmo: "waiting for ipfs....."
hotpotato325: what computer u using?
Nubadoxd: @georgehotz So like I'm a newbie, can you explain briefly what your are doing
two_eight: the matrix PogChamp
dorkmo: "Gateway Timeout"
directrix13: @georgehotz I think that gateway isn't working well
ragemaster999: have you already leaked your ip?
gonzaloquintas: gateway timeout
sirvapealots: @georgehotz what ports does IPFS use?
W1lkins: 22 Kappa
sharmouta: what you up to today yung georgie
jay_al97: https://www.npmjs.com/package/simple-peer
kingkong3211: https://github.com/ipfs/go-ipfs/issues/6383
sirvapealots: don't spam links LUL
sirvapealots: Actually write what you're saying
two_eight: try this random npm package :)
sirvapealots: @two_eight EXACTLY LUL someone understands my sentiments
ragemaster999: just run it on an instance
Jonzuk: you use mac?
sirvapealots: @Jonzuk he doesn't Kappa
Jonzuk: lmfao
w9cceixh24b23ouiljlhmyp1: FYI cloudflare leaks ur IP @footer
sirvapealots: @w9cceixh24b23ouiljlhmyp1 it pulls from IPFS; Calm down dude
rektiw0w: maybe we give up on ipfs?
sirvapealots: @georgehotz yeah you may have to open up a port
directrix13: @georgehotz are you sure your firewall isn't blocking outbound from ipfs?
WarSwick: Did you ever complete the iphone Jailbreak you were doing last time on stream?
sirvapealots: @directrix13 ISP's block ports; you need to use higher ports, to route things :)
directrix13: right, but so does any firewall running on that computer
lchowderl: What kind of keyboard do you use boss man?
harmanthebest1: new series self compiling compiler
sirvapealots: @directrix13 yeah but that's easy to resolve, compared to ISP's blocking them
sirvapealots: @directrix13 just use higher port numbers 4Head
sirvapealots: @georgehotz now you feel the pain of network engineers LUL LUL LUL LUL LUL LUl
Gentris: !time
Gentris: !uptime
sirvapealots: webui should work Pog
yaus_baus: middle finger on forehead = big brain time
sirvapealots: LINK AGAIN
sirvapealots: POGGERS
georgehotz: https://cloudflare-ipfs.com/ipfs/QmfWYwhPjzBHcdaN2bhwDYU8WuDHBZhvwQUCQvBokUu8JK/
carbonchain: So slow
gonzaloquintas: nothing yet
dorkmo: "waitingggg'''''
unique_ptr_: just loading
rektiw0w: the title loads...
directrix13: can anybody pull /ipfs/QmbM8nAZJkTyAQM7c3EyeH2Y2xhqzS6wfcoBG9FKn1jut4 ?
1monkjuice: looks like its not serving the src's
rudolphdoesgames: loaded
vmarkushin: loaded!
sirvapealots: maybe cloudflare haven't recognized it yet @georgehotz
foti_kasparov: loaded
1monkjuice: yeye
gonzaloquintas: im in!
XeroKool: Works
Arksam: Keepo
Datamaskin: works
gankeomenores: works
Ziv0: works
yaus_baus: worked
gankeomenores: i won
nicovzq: hotz u r the man!
champ900: i lost
zeroeagle1: damm i lost
zeroeagle1: fking hard game
yaus_baus: cheats for this??
W1lkins: just beat whatever idiot was playing against me, ez
CSbps: works
zeroeagle1: feel better :)
carbonchain: some tricks ya @zeroeagle1
gonzaloquintas: when players tie, it keeps saying whos next
sirvapealots: THE REAL CHALLENGE LUL
zeroeagle1: will you put that on ur resume for the world changing startup
sirvapealots: @georgehotz you need sessions
Jonzuk: how much do you make on AI
yaus_baus: 3.50
adibaby04: i thought this was regex
whichtom: that was a while ago
crazywulf770: i would not learn react if i am rich... so maybe he is broke
crazywulf770: :-D
georgehotz: https://github.com/geohot/twitchtactoe
leopp: !uptime
georgehotz: pull request for tie?
zeroeagle1: will you put that on ur resume for the world changing startup
Arksam: LUL
dorkmo: pull request for connect4 plz
rektiw0w: me :)
CaptainAshtar: oyy web :) nice you do even web ...
CaptainAshtar: wtf
CaptainAshtar: you are a serious person Hotz ...
Nubadoxd: I don't know what I understand less, what chat says sometimes, or h
flips_hope: LUL
CaptainAshtar: StinkyCheese
Nubadoxd: George's constant 4 head touching shedLife
Nubadoxd: He's re
Nubadoxd: my God this keyboard sucks ....
BiszkopTT: js god
th3_maj0r: 17yo hack iphone, 30yo create tic tac toe
BiszkopTT: @th3_maj0r the journey
nicovzq: hahahah
CaptainAshtar: haha
YouPowerRush: 123 or wat ?
rektiw0w: @th3_maj0r MuLTIPLAYER* tic tac toe
th3_maj0r: oh
CaptainAshtar: he created skynet
Nubadoxd: wait George is 30? shedShock
directrix13: all data goes into state
Arksam: Twitchtactoc*
nicovzq: !uptime
BiszkopTT: worldwideeeeeeeee
yaus_baus: george is Timeless
nicovzq: !help
real_selkie: react sucks
Ziv0: it does need to be in a state
BiszkopTT: @real_selkie STOP
leopp: make it battle royale tic tac toe
Arksam: Jebaited /
W1lkins: create a constructor
W1lkins: and do it in that
CaptainAshtar: make it 3D opengl tic tac toe
WendellSwan: i always enjoy watching these streams but i never have any idea whats going on
Nubadoxd: Oh yeah, this is a lot better. shedPat
HuntMePls: @georgehotz you can use variables in a class as long as they are in a constructor
nicovzq: @WendellSwan same
yamchah2: show us your vimrc Pog
restitutione: put in {}
yaus_baus: its on his git
yaus_baus: configuration repo
WendellSwan: i know how to print hello world in python
anguscupcake: this is good coding ASMR
W1lkins: add it to a constructor in Game
Nubadoxd: ASMR KEKKW
Nubadoxd: KEKW
restitutione:
two_eight: those topre sounds Kreygasm
kingkong3211: @georgehotz this might be useful https://github.com/madou/react-peer
Nubadoxd: ^
yamchah2: 9 line vimrc what a legend
yaus_baus: real coder vimrc
Ziv0: LUL
yaus_baus: lmfao
michael_laurent: LuL
A_Big_Sandwich: LUL
two_eight: typescript version of jsx
rektiw0w: tsx monkaS
frediiiez: LUL
Jo__: LYL
Nubadoxd: KEKW
Jo__: damn
CaptainAshtar: why this guy is screaming?
Jo__: LUL
brisingr1031: @georgehotz a car
nicovzq: hahahha
data_day_life: tittysex, obvi
yaus_baus: TSX????
XeroKool: LUL
NeolexBZH: @georgehotz why did you stopped hacking ?
MuscleMario: typescript is what ppl write w/ but yeah, it iz 3 much
yaus_baus: DELETE THIS
jbyte1988: pinga
foxubu: :D
Nubadoxd: tittysex KEKW
W1lkins: make an issue on Github Kappa
reaganchisholm: looool
HuntMePls: LUL
directrix13: modified javascript I believe
yaus_baus: someone clip that
directrix13: like template language or something?
Jeppelelle: impeach tsx:ers
data_day_life: ismCOP
foxubu: George is gonna fry their repo with a friendly pull request lol
nicovzq: why ppl make it so complex? D:
yaus_baus: is this just an excuse for george to write js?
Nubadoxd: Well... is it?
Brohanson: limmySteel
mlgdotca: => binds the context of this cuz js is fukt
yaus_baus: tsx confirmed trigger
nicovzq: !donate
jay_al97: tsx is typescript and jsx
Nubadoxd: ^
rektiw0w: so compiling it will turn it into regular react jsx?
HuntMePls: tsx comes from typescript, its a javascript library that provides javascript with variables type-checking like declaring a variable int or string
yaus_baus: tic tac toe battle royale???
benakiba: Pog
mkc0de: @georgehotz ohh react. what's with discord?
logicssoldier: Typescript is great but luv u
Santiago_LHC: #vanillaJS
zoki_macola: George is boomer
rektiw0w: forms in react are not nice
Nubadoxd: @georgehotz can you add particle effects for when someone wins/loses/ties? shedHeart
Santiago_LHC: kids nowadays getting fancy with them frameworks
directrix13: Typescript is Javascript#
Jewishrambo: do preventdefault
god_damn: @Jewishrambo doesnt need to submit so theres no need
JdPaulBlart: lmao i just got done making tic tac toe using gtk in c nice timing
mkc0de: chat has he created discord server?
trchaosTR: this is the first time i see a mod in george's chat
Nubadoxd: They are silent snipers shedScared
reaganchisholm: pass the onclick event to get the value
chagasf: this.connect.bind(this)
logicssoldier: you do have an event ;)
Abnormmall: this.onSubmit.bind(this)
rektiw0w: u have to save the value of the box into state
reaganchisholm: onClick=
mkc0de: just use arrow func
reaganchisholm: access the value with event.target.value
reaganchisholm: something like that
mkc0de: bind for boomers
logicssoldier: oh right you need to setState w/ text box input onChange event
W1lkins: just add an id to the element and rip it out of the page with document.getElementById LUL
logicssoldier: FailFish
Santiago_LHC: #vanillaJSshit
directrix13: oh lordy
yaus_baus: ok Boomer
mkc0de: var NotLikeThis
chagasf: you can use ref, or state
GOLDSOULTHEORY: var Pog
logicssoldier: onChange=)};
directrix13: ^^^
chagasf: onClick=
logicssoldier: you dont have to bind
jay_al97: use => so you don't have to bind
logicssoldier: ^^
FlySociety2o9: not bind need3ed
Nubadoxd: ^
logicssoldier: lambdas preserve scope
logicssoldier: so no need to bind
do_not_erase: onClick => connect()
logicssoldier: connect = () =>
W1lkins: since it's in a lambda now you actually need to call connect
W1lkins: this.connect()
logicssoldier: connect should be a lambda!!
W1lkins: before it was invoked automatically
gseven_: this.connect() not this.connect
dorkmo: tic tac toe player lobby
ruslik_: LUL
two_eight: don't discuss a man's monitor size
Arksam: riPepperonis
GOLDSOULTHEORY: LUL
yaus_baus: lmao
anguscupcake: bruh monitor size is OFF LIMITS
kytos1k: LUL
Jo__: ahahah
httpsdubdubdotcomm: lol
yaus_baus: just had to do it to em'
dorkmo: Corgo1
logicssoldier: dont disrespekt the monitor size
Vilebiscuit: Hi guys, I am planning on learning machine learning. Where do you guys recommend I start, udacity or some other place?
Santiago_LHC: #IGUESS
Forbaya: lmao
yaus_baus: bro george is the best
BiszkopTT: had to do it to em
martinkirilov: because monitor size and keyboard aren't preferences, you better have same as him or you will not be approved
httpsdubdubdotcomm: small monitor and loud keyboard... was that the insult ...wud i miss..?
do_not_erase: onClick=
httpsdubdubdotcomm: just tuned in
yaus_baus: no keyboard talk here
directrix13: does react have a virtual dom?
restitutione: yes debugger;
BiszkopTT: @do_not_erase dis
yaus_baus: no hardware talk
Vilebiscuit: Hi guys, I am planning on learning machine learning. Where do you guys recommend I start, udacity or some other place?
martinkirilov: @yaus_baus no talk
Forbaya: yeah don't talk here please
do_not_erase: Your setting the value of connect not calling the function ^^
yaus_baus: @Vilebiscuit check out sentedex on youtube
BiszkopTT: this chat is my safe space so just shh
two_eight: just start listening to what your machine is saying. that is the first step to learning
kytos1k: SeemsGood
logicssoldier: @do_not_erase BlessRNG
logicssoldier: check out @do_not_erase
bsx1123: @Vilebiscuit fast.ai is the best ml course on the web
anguscupcake: dont click that link
tornpaperyoyos: @Vilebiscuit https://www.udemy.com/course/deeplearning/ https://www.udemy.com/course/artificial-intelligence-az/
do_not_erase: onClick=
BiszkopTT: dont need the braces i think
Vilebiscuit: thanks a lot guys
yaus_baus: i heard siraj raval can teach you AI in 5 minutes
whichtom: lmao
kytos1k: LUL
BiszkopTT: no u need my bad Kappa
httpsdubdubdotcomm: @Vilebiscuit opencv may help along your learning path. idk
W1lkins: yaus_baus LUL
init2: Hey, guys, what's up?
deadbeatdad7: just smoking weed and watching the stream bro 👍
kytos1k: SeemsGood
Vesh: im out of weed some one for me aswell @deadbeatdad7
NonTrivial778: are you on drugs right now?
yaus_baus: is coffee a drug
BiszkopTT: debuggin with console log is best kind of debugging
BiszkopTT: @yaus_baus yea its a stimulant
ragemaster999: we need a leaderboard
El1T3MaN: @georgehotz you live in a studio apartment?
tornpaperyoyos: im ready im ready im ready
Bitcoin__: I remember making a Ultimate Tic Tac Toe game in VB.Net when I was younger
brisingr1031: @georgehotz what kind of ice cubss do you use?? /s
iron_lasagna: maybe Ninja will play it :)
martinkirilov: gonna be a long stream, cool
two_eight: need hook up google ads as well
walktheabyss: walktheabyss subscribed with Twitch Prime.
yaus_baus: microtransations please
martinkirilov: ingame life purchases
Santiago_LHC: It also needs a DLC
KNOOKEL_HEAD: React PogCHamp
BiszkopTT: dlc with battleships
martinkirilov: every turn is 100 bits
KNOOKEL_HEAD: PogChamp
Santiago_LHC: Needs accomplishments
brisingr1031: ratirlFlex
MrTriharder: Geohot doing JavaScript DansGame not my george DansGame
martinkirilov: and hours played
Luccaasss: what programming language is that:
Luccaasss: ?
yaus_baus: paypal george 5$ to have blue X instead of black
tornpaperyoyos: are we ging to have player skins as well??? @georgehotz
iron_lasagna: Needs loot boxes
httpsdubdubdotcomm: can we bet wit bits with this game?
schadowman: @Luccaasss js
Santiago_LHC: @Luccaasss JS
rauluz: yo guys, u can use react for back end too?
martinkirilov: we need X and O skins
BiszkopTT: @Luccaasss js and framework is react
two_eight: @Luccaasss modern javascript :) beautiful ain't it?
okeeeeeee: can you implement this variation? https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ultimate_tic-tac-toe @georgehotz
MrTriharder: @georgehotz are u working with WebRtc
rektiw0w: setState george
MrTriharder: oh hes using simplepeer.js
MrTriharder: cool library
MrTriharder: had used it for video calling SeemsGood
kratosboii: oh no
MrTriharder: PogChamp
razr22: pog
MuscleMario: lol
W1lkins: PogChamp
iron_lasagna: PogChamp
KNOOKEL_HEAD: PogChamp you're nuts
Luccaasss: you're a jeanus
init2: SuperHaxor!!!111
frediiiez: PogChamp
Abnormmall: LMFAOOOOOOOOO
kytos1k: PogChamp
kratosboii: PogChamp
Bitcoin__: !donate
MrTriharder: No Server communication PogChamp
ragemaster999: PogChamp
garam_chai94: PogChamp
mixxaww: PogChamp PogChamp
cjocol2201: Kreygasm
Abnormmall: PogU
dekassssss: Pog
garam_chai94: !uptime
nesbyy1: Pog
martinkirilov: PogCahmp
martinkirilov: PogChamp
init2: EIEIO
KNOOKEL_HEAD: same port PogChamp
luismario0o: He did it, boys
yaus_baus: lmao
soiax_: PogChamp
Luccaasss: PogChamp
bsx1123: PogChamp
init2: !uptime
dorkmo: Party1
Dynasmite: port for console Pog
Thobrik: you enjoying this nerdz?
KNOOKEL_HEAD: goated on the stickz PogChamp
JdPaulBlart: next step: use minimax to calculate best move
MrTriharder: @JdPaulBlart or just do if else and write AI Kappa
martinkirilov: FakeClick, the maintainability Kappa
KNOOKEL_HEAD: those clicks Kreygasm
LaunchpadFun: @georgehotz made the PR for the drawn game btw.
kratosboii: god bless vim
kratosboii: and the poeple who made it
KNOOKEL_HEAD: wasnt it just 1 guy
kratosboii: god bless that dude
yaus_baus: bram
JUST_5HEAD: nice branch
deR_Ed: states.PLAYER_X
matejsninja: you need to states.PLAYER_X
josergdev: states.X
edargorter: I used double DQN for tictactoe ... proved quite effective.
deR_Ed: 5Head
matejsninja: or make const  = states;
Cjiq: What are we coding today?
rektiw0w: @kratosboii what makes vim so good?
ragemaster999: use a regex to check the winning condition, for them memes
kratosboii: @rektiw0w r u not watching lol
rektiw0w: @kratosboii well compared to other editors?
razr22: LUL
deR_Ed: golang would like to have a word
kratosboii: just a lot quicker... no bloat too lol
yaus_baus: Tabs in TSX
rektiw0w: computers are fast nowadays a lot of stuff runs fast enough
MonkaSupreme: give link
ragemaster999: use a regex to check the winning condition, for them memes @georgehotz
MoProject: why not use ML algorithms, is a lot faster and less code
kratosboii: not talking about that.. takling about the actual fle editing
Maw3rick: WutFace
rektiw0w: let me beat u on tic tac toe, but promise not to ban
KNOOKEL_HEAD: create-react-app PogChamp
matejsninja: you can make just if(!conn)
jellyjar: no cap, as a noob, this shit is impressive to me
ronniesmiths7: How old were you when you stated to program?
KNOOKEL_HEAD: 1
Santiago_LHC: -2
rektiw0w: george learned how to program right out of the womb
tornpaperyoyos: MEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEE
fourhundredtwenty: me PogChamp
rudolphdoesgames: not me
kingkong3211: me
kratosboii: meeeeeee
Maw3rick: Lets roolllll
tornpaperyoyos: MEEEEEEEEEEEEE
rektiw0w: i challenged u first
ragemaster999: me
Raiwo: PogChamp
httpsdubdubdotcomm: imma watch
el_pirulote: not me
LaunchpadFun: @georgehotz got the PR ready for Drawn game
TuleFTW: me?
edargorter: tactic toe
httpsdubdubdotcomm: but thanks for streaming @georgehotz and good job with the tic tac toe
crazywulf770: we need a player name field
anguscupcake: tic tac toe makes me angry
georgehotz: https://cloudflare-ipfs.com/ipfs/QmaVi2KEGhvuaK82YCP4SmARMCUV8sJw1f1AWQjeJHnurD/
MonkaSupreme: hcidzdgohxc00000
georgehotz: 2nthkcj2o3w00000
YouPowerRush: DIE DIE DIIE
kingkong3211: eibdntbf4v500000
edargorter: 1oqy54qjumu00000 remote peer id
mrgh0st0: va83o50qe0000000
ragemaster999: broken
Maw3rick: That was me ez
JUST_5HEAD: lmfao
KNOOKEL_HEAD: LMFAO
KNOOKEL_HEAD: AHAHAHAHA
deadpool_reynolds: hahah
mdrake_: we're in
razr22: DEAD LMAO
rudolphdoesgames: u1r6f3yzzaf00000
kratosboii: LOL
razr22: draw
razr22: LUL
httpsdubdubdotcomm: so wait now tic tack toe is a thing.. Can you build tetris next?...
god_damn: george is really about it
frediiiez: LUL
Santiago_LHC: Sick action
Jo__: stream snipe
Caene: 69xjvbxeak300000
georgehotz: rpw4h1g20k000000
anguscupcake: damn that was intense
LaunchpadFun: Yes I did
mdrake_: LIT
yaus_baus: sweating
razr22: very competitive match
martinkirilov: pmmt9opj61q00000
kratosboii: lmao
smakatak: ut0wvx3obek00000
zoki_macola: knees weak, arms are sweaty
MonkaSupreme: 0b0gr288m5sm0000
martinkirilov: tie
razr22: hahahahahahaa
UniversalGeneve: LUL
god_damn: LMFAOOOO
Hunted9000: hajm74e72j500000
god_damn: HE TWIRLS
SuchALuckyGuy: World Championship right here
anguscupcake: I'm on the edge of my seat
mrgh0st0: 4z3cixnh62q00000
MonkaSupreme: LUL
kytos1k: LUL
frediiiez: LUL
tychus07: LUL
httpsdubdubdotcomm: congrats!
razr22: q2p7uqb32gc00000
MonkaSupreme: tunpvcs2reg00000
httpsdubdubdotcomm: hell ya good times
cjocol2201: TakeNRG
Nelzex: yo what editor is that in your bash terminal
tornpaperyoyos: y7w8sgyaejc00000
kratosboii: PogChamp LUL
yaus_baus: hype
UniversalGeneve: real inspiring stuff.
Ziv0: LUL
MoProject: hahah
god_damn: FUCK AMAZON
frediiiez: LUL LUL
piccibrah: yayay boiiii
whichtom: LUL
edargorter: 1oqy54qjumu00000
rektiw0w: 7h79bqn8n5800000
BambiPT: fuck googleeeeeeee bruuuu
kingkong3211: loololo
FlySociety2o9: LUL
MorningScifi: haha fuck google we have tic tac toe
mixxaww: LUL
yaus_baus: future is here boys
KNOOKEL_HEAD: TRUEEEEEEEE LUL
kratosboii: HAHAHAH
HorseRacing4Life: @Nelzex it's vi
El1T3MaN: what server he used to deploy it on?
anguscupcake: yea fuck facebook we have react
speeddrawing101: TRUEEEEEEEEEEEEE
SuchALuckyGuy: WutFace
Nelzex: MIDDLE OUT ENCRYPTION!!!!
Xaotic: is he using vscode?
zoki_macola: neighbours are wondering right now
GeneralSoak: its the new new internet?
Nelzex: HOOLI CHAT
Hunted9000: cym6wjrc42a00000
JUST_5HEAD: Kappa
kingkong3211: congress doesnt do shit
FlySociety2o9: HOOLI
tychus07: fuck facebook -> react yo
god_damn: please say it louder for the people in the back
dawgwhisper007: omg shut up
Harm133: dont you work for google LUL
LaunchpadFun: @Xaotic Vim
alexdickson98: ni1s6q46kqq00000
alreye: you were a intern at facebook.. why you trashig them
imamazing87: PogChamp
frediiiez: TRUE
AbnerSK: 2wizgjltt6z00000
Xaotic: Hooli
dawgwhisper007: you might end up working there
dawgwhisper007: stop
schadowman: you worked for google LUL
jellyjar: time to meditate again
tornpaperyoyos: dch1k5gz3sw00000
Hunted9000: 1p41wvgm26b00000
init2: Evilcorps
yaus_baus: george dont work for the man
SHINO5454: Richard?
smakatak: Hooli > PiedPiper
dawgwhisper007: this is recorded you know
FlySociety2o9: George to Google confirmed LUL
picklesareok: but google says do no evil LUL
dawgwhisper007: stop!!!
razr22: 2wi37bbfndg00000
alreye: He's mad because he got fired
Nelzex: MIDDLE OUT ENCRYPTION 4.00 weisman SCORE!
init2: @georgehotz What do u think about school 42?
Caene: weEEEeEEeee aRe tHe iNtErNet
MorningScifi: we'll become our own google... with blackjack.. and..
rektiw0w: would u work for elon musk?
FlySociety2o9: HAHAHAHA
UniversalGeneve: @georgehotz GANs for next stream?
SuchALuckyGuy: Well there goes his possible internship
yaus_baus: go off george
chagasf: hahahahahahahaha
alexdickson98: 3841rg8p8bv00000
Santiago_LHC: #COMEATME
JdPaulBlart: beat sony now hes gonna beat google PogChamp
zoki_macola: so much energy
speeddrawing101: YOU ARE SO HYPE @georgehotz
smakatak: 5.4 wiseman score
imamazing87: any gifters in shifters
suteki1: cw2l18irx8h00000
chaprio1: george would rather work for sony
TheNakedFlame: Hacking Google with Tic Tac Toe React sodaAgent
dawgwhisper007: so you are the best dev in the world?
alreye: We need decentralized comma ai
Nelzex: 6.0 WEISMAN SCORE
kingkong3211: make a decentralised interned
suteki1: pfxjb7eiae000000
kingkong3211: internet
garam_chai94: LUL
KNOOKEL_HEAD: F A C K GOOBLE
god_damn: LUL
Artistxtv: @georgehotz did you teach yourself everything about coding?
tychus07: LUL yo shit don't work yo
MonkaSupreme: LUL
frediiiez: @alexdickson98make your move bro
kratosboii: LUL
Nelzex: 7.0 WEISMANN SCORE
alexdickson98: d86wl6leaqw00000
AbnerSK: n36h0rt8ev000000
alexlucas_: PogChamp
dawgwhisper007: you just learned about regular expressions!!!
Alevsk: if someday i see you on the streets can i ask for a selfie with you?
rebuhleiv: what do you think about that ipfs files are not persistent? you cant be safe that your files get lost
asafshshshsh2121: 1ik51jvbjyc00000
sultantw: send the link
Celestial_Jaeger: @georgehotz did you go to uni and where?
yaus_baus: george living in 4050
dawgwhisper007: @georgehotz you just learned regex!
smakatak: I just got 8.2 Weismann score beat that motherfckers
httpsdubdubdotcomm: okay @georgehotz may we build some AI to compete against?
tornpaperyoyos: ayyyy that was me
alexdickson98: @georgehotz make it so that it is random who starts not always the guest
AbnerSK: o0pttlzg2ms00000
suteki1: 890rm25kwb000000
frediiiez: @asafshshshsh2121 gg
Nelzex: mIDDLE out EncryTIon! PIED PIPER WAY GANG SHIZZLE
LaunchpadFun: @georgehotz I have a PR opne for Draw
kingkong3211: why 2020 though?
dawgwhisper007: @georgehotz the rant is immortalized forever!!!
restitutione: @georgehotz Ultimate tic-tac-toe would be cool
chaprio1: who's gonna torn them apart tho
SilvanoGJr: here's a dude from Brazil thankful to this guy for allowing us to have iphone's in our local carriers
FargioFarmani: ifl5gompu8000000
tychus07: tic tac to is stupid make the one with 9 tables (kinda like sudoku)
Nelzex: yo geo how u get so good at vim and shit
Artistxtv: @georgehotz did you teach yourself everything about coding?
kratosboii: Hopefully torn apart because theyre scum bags
KNOOKEL_HEAD: @georgehotz how do i invest in IPFS PogChamp
Ziv0: tic tac toe battle royale when?
asafshshshsh2121: @frediiiez gg
frediiiez: @suteki1 gg
jrogan993: nah the new stuff will be hobbyist FANG will rule forever
my_curiosity: what do you mean shape up?
dorkmo: the only way f
suteki1: @frediiiez gg
Nelzex: !keyboard
Maw3rick: SeemsGood
TheKoreanZombi: Code review!
FargioFarmani: ofm5vns29rq00000
W1lkins: winner == 'draw' DansGame
tornpaperyoyos: @georgehotz do it one mo gain
rebuhleiv: ipfs files are not persistent. what to do about it? the files are lost if nobody is seeding
frediiiez: @FargioFarmani you won m8
smakatak: Guys we need AGILE SCRUM this is a chaos
kingkong3211: @georgehotz do you take interns at commai.ai
jbyte1988: 0hir9zoyocqn0000
FargioFarmani: lmao @frediiiez
alexdickson98: keeps sending ids @chat
httpsdubdubdotcomm: has anyone messed with the open bci yet? curious on openions.
frediiiez: @FargioFarmani LUL
MorningScifi: Yes can we have a 1 hour meeting where we talk about the future of this project
MorningScifi: hahaha
Caene: I mean, it's JS, it's supposed to look like shit.
archeadis: whats the one line for that in python? @georgehotz
tornpaperyoyos: @georgehotz play again
alreye: @georgehotz Explain why please
KNOOKEL_HEAD: @georgehotz how do i invest in IPFS PogChamp
jrogan993: decentralized internet will never become mainstream
FargioFarmani: lhrgketpez000000
GeneralSoak: yeah torrents are back
yaus_baus: @alreye bro the gov is coming for our tendies
alexdickson98: @georgehotz have u wath tv show silicon valley
Nelzex: GUYS HOOLI IS THE FUTURE
Nelzex: HOOLI CHAT
LiIDrunk: future of ads though ?? LUL
frediiiez: @FargioFarmani gg!
SilvanoGJr: @jrogan993 horses are faster
bytecube: @georgehotz did you ever look at the iota protocol?
god_damn: limewire is making a comeback
FargioFarmani: again you? @frediiiez
alreye: @yaus_baus but but but... why?
razr22: h8yzwlvgaa000000
frediiiez: @FargioFarmani lmao yes
rektiw0w: d83plm12m7000000
Ziv0: LUL
JUST_5HEAD: LOL
Vesh: LUL
chaprio1: LOL
Celestial_Jaeger: decentralized OMEGALUL
ragemaster999: LOL
Alevsk: fail
KNOOKEL_HEAD: lmfao
schadowman: decentralized LUL
FlySociety2o9: LUK
Vesh: lmao LUL
god_damn: LMFAOOO
chaprio1: google already on it
chaprio1: KEKW
yaus_baus: limewire: nickleback.exe
frediiiez: @rektiw0w gg i won Kappa
GeneralSoak: why'd you give up on the self driving stuff
rektiw0w: @frediiiez nooooob easyyyyyyyy
Ziv0: there's also peertube
frediiiez: LUL
kytos1k: jeah like emule serverless
kingkong3211: do you take interns at commai.ai?#
LiIDrunk: google just completed 6500 mile private undersea cable
Artistxtv: @georgehotz why do programmers use macOS?
rebuhleiv: george. can you elaborate on how and where the files at ipfs are stored? if nobody is seeding you loose your files! so you need a server which is not decentralized
chaprio1: monkaS
chaprio1: banned
Caene: @GeneralSoak Google.
yaus_baus: @kingkong3211 no comma talk here
FlySociety2o9: monkaS
NonTrivial778: can you win this competition https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qQ-56b_LvOw ?
hmmmu: i prefer redtube
archeadis: @georgehotz do you watch porn? real talk
kingkong3211: do you take interns at commai.ai?
god_damn: maybe you cant
bytecube: @georgehotz did you ever look at the IOTA protocol?
hoffs: should comma be nationalized
Celestial_Jaeger: i just wonder why is it not allowed to be discussed? is there something involving the law
kratosboii: really miss when porn was decentralized too !
rektiw0w: so how do u feel now as an indie game developer? @georgehotz
alexdickson98: @georgehotz do you think everything is invented?
Yeahsper: @archeadis Who doesn't?
archeadis: @Yeahsper george might not
init2: @georgehotz the consiracy bigger than all of us
GeneralSoak: do you still work on it full time?
init2: The top one percent of top one percent
my_curiosity: but the thing is
LiIDrunk: yea true
frediiiez: @georgehotz Have you seen Mr. Robot?
NonTrivial778: thats porn geohot
god_damn: @jbyte1988 no ones laughing
suteki1: @jbyte1988 shut up degen
alexdickson98: dont enter the link its porn @georgehotz
Celestial_Jaeger: science is discovered, engineering technology is invented
rektiw0w: @jbyte1988 good troll man wow u are funny
zoki_macola: there is dtube also
speeddrawing101: @GeneralSoak you're close to getting banned, not allowed to talk about comma in here buddy
NonTrivial778: dtube is garbage
alreye: yo yo yo brotha you need some mods
zoki_macola: maybe idk
yaus_baus: mods afk
Fatmetheny: @jbyte1988 George ban this dude
alreye: @yaus_baus mod is busy checking out the link LUL
suteki1: @jbyte1988
schadowman: works real well Kappa
LiIDrunk: you are saying gov provide hardware reqs for people ??
Vesh: jbyte
LaunchpadFun: spamming
Vesh: ban his ass
alexdickson98: @jbyte1988
kratosboii: jbyte
bytecube: @georgehotz i would like to hear your opinion on the IOTA protocol. https://www.iota.org/.
tornpaperyoyos: @jbyte1988
yaus_baus: yeeted
Vesh: cya nerd HeyGuys
LiIDrunk: you are saying gov provide hardware reqs for people ?? @georgehotz
KNOOKEL_HEAD: LUL what a cuck
suteki1: @georgehotz what keyboard do you use? Kappa
dorkmo: twister.net.co
KNOOKEL_HEAD: AHHAHAHAHAHAH
yaus_baus: bro i have 1000 iota coin
yaus_baus: feelsbad
god_damn: LMFAOOOO
frediiiez: thoughts on Monero @georgehotz
tornpaperyoyos: "quantum computing resistant" wtf LUL
LiIDrunk: you are saying gov provide hardware requirements of internet for people ??
yaus_baus: /s/s/s/s/s/s
bytecube: haha, thanks 😀
razr22: f
KNOOKEL_HEAD: LUL
alreye: @georgehotz what do you think of tron?
MorningScifi: everyone divested the moment you said it
yaus_baus: bro they stole my iota
my_curiosity: "real coin" - do you mean the US dollar?
KNOOKEL_HEAD: TRON LUL
MonkaSupreme: buy buy buy
suteki1: FeelsBadMan
ItsKalu: Have you tried doing any AR apps ?
frediiiez: any thoughts on Monero? @georgehotz
dawgwhisper007: what the fuck you dont know how to say ternary??? @georgehotz
dorkmo: iota.org clip art lol
Xaotic: cant believe he is using chrome instead of mozilla lol
elite_elite1: criticizing google and using chrome LUL
dawgwhisper007: ternary operator : ?
kratosboii: sponsored by IOTA
god_damn: 🤨 ah my brain i see... right...
mdrake_: spintronics LUL good god
W1lkins: ternary and trinary are related dawgwhisper007
Caene: Fuck em
Vjasal: sure Kapp
alreye: @georgehotz It sounds like these guys are actually thinking about the future...
KNOOKEL_HEAD: IOTA ? sell : buy thats the real ternary
mdrake_: nice
yaus_baus: ill be laughing in 2050 when ill buy twitchtactoe with my iota coins
init2: Troika? Is that like Russian triple?
Vjasal: brain comping technology :o
hmmmu: that looks like my homework
W1lkins: iota ? implement own crypto badly : take off the shelf crypto
ChocolaateRain: harvard boys LULW
roletro: they were sudents
crispi____: LUL
yunidoo: hi @georgehotz, first time i've seen your channel, are you regularly on twitch doing programming/tech?
Artistxtv: why is @georgehotz not verified on twitch @twitch lmao
Quad___lol: crypto is my favorite scam
Santiago_LHC: They wrote a paper. It has to be serious Kappa
god_damn: B) SPEARHEADING INNOVATION
W1lkins: Vulnerabilities must march on :)
KNOOKEL_HEAD: LMFAO
crispi____: LUL
frediiiez: any thoughts on Monero?
anguscupcake: lol
MorningScifi: spoken like a true cult leader
MorningScifi: haha
mariusmafius: pompous marketing shiet
dawgwhisper007: they are harvard kids though
NonTrivial778: we are not smart as you
TuleFTW: u heard of ben goetzel?
ckrpasa: you should upload a setup video for open pilot on youtube because when people heard something different they looks it on youtube
Vjasal: spearheading technology PogChamp
Quad___lol: Progress must march on! We will accomplish 5 year plan in 4 years!
kratosboii: geo, please spearhead crypto
wiseai: KEKW
LiIDrunk: whats made for everybody should be approved by everybody as well
imlewpie: @georgehotz how did you learn ML in the beginning ?
yaus_baus: this is a decentralized cult @MorningScifi
alreye: @georgehotz they sound like alyssa holmes LUL
roletro: it's pronounced ket-chak
KNOOKEL_HEAD: sPEaRheaDIng tEChn0LOgY
imamazing87: @georgehotz what keybored good for programming ?
adibaby04: https://github.com/adiprerepa vet my github
TheNakedFlame: George spearheaded Tic Tac Toe technology 😎
tornpaperyoyos: @imamazing87 whatever feels good for you or is your favorite
frediiiez: any thoughts on Monero @georgehotz ?
wiseai: Kappa
hmmmu: Kappa
god_damn: gods work
yaus_baus: george ruining my crypto portfolio
yaus_baus: feelsbad
KNOOKEL_HEAD: TETHER OMEGALUL
KNOOKEL_HEAD: TOTALLY BACKED
yunidoo: hi @georgehotz, first time i've seen your channel, are you regularly on twitch doing programming/tech?
alreye: @georgehotz what do you think of TRON?
imamazing87: @tornpaperyoyos thanks <3
mariusmafius: "lost"
Sarkin_dota: @yunidoo no
whichtom: it is rather disconcerting how many of these are scams
hmmmu: thoughs on NEO @georgehotz
LiIDrunk: in the end all of the crypto will drown anyway
ragemaster999: tether is backed up with real currency right?
frediiiez: how about Monero?
MonkaSupreme: ETC
Santiago_LHC: When are we making our own crypto on stream? Twitchcoin?
yunidoo: thanks @Sarkin_dota so how do you guys know when he's here?
ELITEGAMS: 13 is okay but shady
alreye: @georgehotz TRON bought bittorrent
kratosboii: short all scam crypto
picklesareok: what do you like about the others?
Arksam: What about brave's Basic Attention Token (BAT) ?
r000sh: F crypto. Now everyone must dive in AGI. LoL
Sarkin_dota: @yunidoo , you can turn on notifications
KNOOKEL_HEAD: @georgehotz Tether has more volume than BTC which is pretty concerning
dawgwhisper007: unnecessary enemies
LiIDrunk: F crypto
anguscupcake: chainlink?
Sarkin_dota: @yunidoo will tell you whenever he goes online, which from my experience, is like once in 2 weeks or so
revenantrazer: how do you gauge what is a scan or not?
kajizzlewat: @georgehotz NANO seems very interesting
GOLDSOULTHEORY: What constitutes a cryptocurrency being a scam?
dawgwhisper007: @georgehotz unnecessary enemies what if they invested in comma.ai
daxyxy98: zcash just pays the founder an insane tax OMEGALUL
frediiiez: do you have Monero?
yunidoo: @Sarkin_dota ah, so no advance notice, ok thanks for your help
unique_ptr_: i only belive in dogecoin
snapcs1: so many people investing when they dont understand shit
alreye: All these coins defeat the purpose of cryptocurrency...
daxyxy98: its dead
smurfd0: isnt crypto overall dodgy?
elite_elite1: @georgehotz why do you use chrome instead of firefox?
ezraflag: bitconnect Kappa
Quad___lol: someone should mark a pyramid schema based on crypto...
Quad___lol: make*
daxyxy98: zclassic made bitcoin private which was kinda scammy
alreye: biiittttconnneccttt
adibaby04: @georgehotz vet github i want to be roasted https://github.com/adiprerepa
Alevsk: what about Stellar Lumens? they are giving away for free from time to time to keybase users
School47: zcash is a scam. YOu can't be sure about total suppy of coin @georgehotz
anguscupcake: lmao
KNOOKEL_HEAD: @georgehotz Tether has more volume than BTC which is pretty concerning
ChocolaateRain: zclassic is a fork of zcash great classic
whichtom: i don't get the point of crypto
imamazing87: best strean every <3
imamazing87: stream*
hmmmu: should i sell my house and buy btc cash?
snapcs1: yes
revenantrazer: lol
School47: @hmmmu yes
Maw3rick: RPGAyaya
Quad___lol: @hmmmu yes absolutely
Santiago_LHC: LOBBY
KNOOKEL_HEAD: you should do React more often PogChamp press 1 if you agree
Artistxtv: to this day i still don't understand how bitcoin works lol.
NonTrivial778: I think Elon Musk loves ethereum
elite_elite1: @georgehotz checkout siacoin/sia tech. thoughts on it?
BambiPT: sell you virtual soul and buy btc cash
alexdickson98: @georgehotz the player starting should be random not always guest
alienware997: alienware997 subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 3 months! Greetings from germany!
dorkmo: Party1
M03x: what he s working on ??
hoffs: decentralized internet
snapcs1: it says in the title?
Anakat: twitchtactoe
josergdev: a9bmiu1k1eq00000
LiIDrunk: make it work without sharing peerId
KNOOKEL_HEAD: peer to peer tic tac toe @M03x
M03x: @KNOOKEL_HEAD for twitch ?
KNOOKEL_HEAD: for anyone
mailboxbandit1: Hey man been a fan since the iPhone unlock. I'm from upstate New York and was wondering how your time at RIT was?
chriswolfdesign: @georgehotz, I'm a novice web dev looking into publishing my own web apps. What service are you using and how much does it cost?
okeeeeeee: fw9ffeun9r000000 :)
LiIDrunk: use rsa
Maw3rick: @okeeeeeee link
LiIDrunk: to gen key pair as peerId
do_not_erase: how do you force window to side like that on mac?
jmc516: Base it off a queue
jmc516: All I got
MorningScifi: What do you want the lobby to do?
LiIDrunk: use rsa to gen peerId
ELITEGAMS: lobby like a room ?
ragemaster999: have you googled it?
W1lkins: do_not_erase using spectacle
schadowman: not decentralized MonkaSupreme
zeroeagle1: do you have an event or something when someone disconnect?
MorningScifi: Will the lobby auto match people?
josergdev: what
tornpaperyoyos: DAMN IT I FUCKED IT UP
jrogan993: will the lobby have skill based match making?
alexdickson98: automatch is better than lobby
LeeRoy_227: you could have won that one
Vjasal: missed lethal
grey_street: missed lethal
NackterZeuS: NackterZeuS subscribed with Twitch Prime.
yaus_baus: tictactoe elo
ELITEGAMS: Create a new lobby with maxPlayers. Every time someone joins or leaves the lobby, it will fire a callback event of the form???
tornpaperyoyos: I was so close lol
alexlucas_: elo rank
hmmmu: george u need an mmr system with ranks
W1lkins: MMR system Kappa
Cjiq: 11 4 Kappa
chocolatechp: abosolutely
Vjasal: add chat
MorningScifi: Have a button for trash talk and a button for positive vibes
yaus_baus: 5k mmr tictactoe
KNOOKEL_HEAD: Rank 1 Peer To Peer Tic Tac Toe Player PogChamp
TheNakedFlame: Create skins for tic tac toe boards
revenantrazer: @hmmmu do you play dota?
NackterZeuS: cheers
unique_ptr_: should create a rank system then you can create a skill based lobby :D
yum72: and paid skins for 'O's and X's
daxyxy98: daxyxy98 subscribed with Twitch Prime.
hmmmu: @revenantrazer sadly yes
Alevsk: add a subscription plan
okeeeeeee: all tic toc tow pros played dota
revenantrazer: @hmmu nice
razr22: fill the page with g ads
jellyjar: needs more microtransactions
KNOOKEL_HEAD: your vim theme is so ugly i actually love it
tornpaperyoyos: YEEEEEESSSSSS
tornpaperyoyos: I WIIIIIIINNN
gutschilino: @georgehotz why do you have a smartwatch?
zeroeagle1: how will you handle when someone disconnect?
tornpaperyoyos: MY LIFE IS COMPLETE
revenantrazer: doa 4 by 4 tictactoe
yaus_baus: @KNOOKEL_HEAD thats what unriced vim looks like lol
soisoisoi: put that in your resume
tornpaperyoyos: i can die happy now that i beat goergoe at tic tac toe LUL
KNOOKEL_HEAD: @yaus_baus unriced LMFAO
hmmmu: @georgehotz where can i buy cosmetics?
tornpaperyoyos: thats getting printed out and put on my refrigerator LUL
W1lkins: unriced is the normal word for it KNOOKEL_HEAD
unique_ptr_: next steam: learning photoshop to create skins for my tictactoe game, implementing microtrasaction
KNOOKEL_HEAD: put that on your resume @tornpaperyoyos
VOR0R: What version of node is he using?
Quad___lol: @georgehotz i see you are good in react. good! our company needs talented react programmers!!! :) what do you think?
yaus_baus: @Quad___lol bruh...
KNOOKEL_HEAD: @W1lkins ok k still funny
tornpaperyoyos: @KNOOKEL_HEAD i will LUL "Oh and i also beat george hotz at tic tac toe" YOURE HIRED IMMEDIATELY
revenantrazer: make thsi version of tictactoe: https://qr.ae/T9aW3h
snapcs1: @W1lkins its definitely not lmfao
Quad___lol: @yaus_baus are you also joining? for you, i would have to an interview tho :/ it looks you are just a poor student trying to learn something here
schadowman: LUL
josergdev: a simple chat
cromed56: !uptime
W1lkins: snapcs1 ricing is the word, so unriced means it hasn't been riced
cromed56: yo george, how long till A.I reigns?
imlewpie: @georgehotz how did you learn ML at first
snapcs1: @W1lkins ight enjoy being racist
ncdoru: ncdoru subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 2 months! Keep up the good work ;)
hmmmu: you need to add VOIP so we can trash talk
unique_ptr_: can you get all of the available id-s? if you can, you can just need to pair them :D
yaus_baus: @Quad___lol im just saying labeling george as a 'react dev' is kind of inaccurate
metis_zver: Why are using React for this game? It's so strangely
W1lkins: snapcs1 it stands for Race Inspired Cosmetic Enhancement. Nothing to do with race bro
Quad___lol: @yaus_baus how come? he is a perfect candidate??!!! he is mastering css and doing some javascript rocket science
th3_maj0r: He is using this game to learn react
Quad___lol: next project - twitch chat voip?
unique_ptr_: @Quad___lol with webrtc i think it is possible
LiIDrunk: create a table of openpeerId's on home page
Fr3fou: hi!!!
Fr3fou: i didn't know you were into react
httpsdubdubdotcomm: xmpp
Fr3fou: :s/var/let/gi
LiIDrunk: create a table of public peerId's on home page which update every time a user connects
Fr3fou: pls
treestompztv: var DansGame
Quad___lol: have i seen a var? cmonBruh
Quad___lol: watchu mean var cmonBruh
domas3210: @treestompztv LUL
KNOOKEL_HEAD: LUL
Poselsky: Why no ( ) => ? Kappa
matejsninja: im always fascinated about people making open source projects like webrtc and etc
Fr3fou: don't you need some server for P2P
Fr3fou: how does peer.js work
r3mote: Hi
Fr3fou: or backend w/e you wanna call it
W1lkins: peer.js wraps WebRTC Fr3fou
Fr3fou: hm
okkessh: why would you need a server for p2p?
KNOOKEL_HEAD: it wouldnt be p2p then
W1lkins: p2s2p Kappa
Fr3fou: kek
httpsdubdubdotcomm: @matejsninja rtmp stuff is alot of fun to research
Fr3fou: yea i thought it was p2s2p
Fr3fou: or smsht
okkessh: is p2s2p even a thing lol
piccibrah: lol
Fr3fou: idk
KNOOKEL_HEAD: it is now LUL
Fr3fou: it's what i was imagning
Fr3fou: PeerServer To broker connections, PeerJS connects to a PeerServer. Note that no peer-to-peer data goes through the server; The server acts only as a connection broker. PeerServer Cloud If you don't want to run your own PeerServer, we offer a free cloud-hosted version of PeerServer. Official PeerServer!
Fr3fou: 🤔
Fr3fou: what's broker
Poselsky: My dream is to write on keyboard like George. <3
unique_ptr_: broker like in mqtt?
okkessh: it just gets them paired
W1lkins: Poselsky reach for the skies
Poselsky: @W1lkins I'm pretty tall. But not that tall. Kappa
matejsninja: can p2p be for more than 1-1? (probably stupid question :P )
whoislewys: oh chips we doin webRTC?
frankytex: I'm here to learn zie basic
davidabeauchamp: davidabeauchamp subscribed with Twitch Prime. They've subscribed for 2 months, currently on a 1 month streak!
Fr3fou: !uptime
martinstuessy: hey @georgehotz I made a cute lil pull request
fQrgotteN: Did you not use breakpoints?
Fr3fou: what should be in componentDidMount
Fr3fou: tbh
Fr3fou: instead of window.onLoad
Fr3fou: @georgehotz
Fr3fou: that*
Maw3rick: RPGAyaya
im_francuzz: for being a really good programmer what vote of importance you give to mathematic/physic? (in a scale 1/10) @georgehotz
schadowman: LUL
KNOOKEL_HEAD: try using componentDidMount instead of window.onload()
chocolatechp: LULLUL
chocolatechp: LUL
wiseai: hasMods
Fr3fou: @georgehotz yea what @KNOOKEL_HEAD said - make the peer connection in componentDidMount
Fr3fou: and also what's the thing you use which lets you snap windows left and right
Fr3fou: yes
Fr3fou: in game
KNOOKEL_HEAD: no
Fr3fou: should work there
KNOOKEL_HEAD: actually yes in game
KNOOKEL_HEAD: my bad
TheKoreanZombi: spectacle on mac to snap windows
Fr3fou: thanks @TheKoreanZombi
NoPartiesGuy: Why peerjs and not socketio?
Fr3fou: socket.io needs a server
Fr3fou: i guess that's what confused me
1kocer66: hello everyone
Fr3fou: since i've had to use socket.io before and was wondering why does peer.js not need one
ppnn123w: tomorrow is my react test lul
NoPartiesGuy: @Fr3fou that explains a lot
NoPartiesGuy: @ppnn123w people having react tests what LUL
tornpaperyoyos: what is george using to write all of this code?
martinstuessy: @Fr3fou uses webrtc, it's like newer websocket type thing
matejsninja: vim
Fr3fou: yea ik now @martinstuessy
treestompztv: you can ignore that for now
NoPartiesGuy: @tornpaperyoyos good luck learning it for next 2 years :D
martinstuessy: @Fr3fou :)
W1lkins: @georgehotz add .map((i, number) =>
Fr3fou: @georgehotz you need to pass a key so react can know what has changed in the virtual DOM
davidabeauchamp: Just give them a key of the index
ppnn123w: @fr3fou coding test components lifecycle and stuff
Nelzex: how are u making the peer ids?
crazywulf770: nickname field would be cool
Fr3fou: cmonBruh
KNOOKEL_HEAD: LUL
NoPartiesGuy: Everytime you use getElementById in react some small kitten dies Kappa
Fr3fou: bruh
Fr3fou: Everytime you use getElementById in react some small kitten dies Kappa
dorkmo: someone needs to submit a PR to twitchchess with ipfs code
manuchroma: what's he doing today
KNOOKEL_HEAD: getElementByID and window.onload is the new way of using React ! LUL
kzonixcomua: lanaluHacking
TheZeroLimit: lift the seat! Kappa
smakatak: Everytime you use getElementById in react some small kitten dies Kappa
unique_ptr_: this is similar to writing C code in a C 17 project
Santiago_LHC: i43zp6bwi8000000
KNOOKEL_HEAD: if it works it works baby
Fr3fou: @georgehotz pls do :s/var/let/gi
kzonixcomua: writing C code in a C 17 project it is normal practice
W1lkins: someone will refactor the whole thing after this stream in a single PR i'm sure
alreye: Don't use var use let
Fr3fou: me @W1lkins
schadowman: @kzonixcomua Thats not a positive
Fr3fou: uwu
estrangedHD: @W1lkins why after, they're typing as he is Kappa
Nelzex: u can hear the crisp topres in that mf hhkb
Nelzex: mmm
Nelzex: crispyy
Fr3fou: what's your opinion on go after having written in it @georgehotz
Nelzex: @Fr3fou go syntax is difficulllly
crazywulf770: lobby hype
KNOOKEL_HEAD: PogChamp
LiIDrunk: you gotta add the status
TheKoreanZombi: Best lobby
Nelzex: bruh im a fookin c# noobski trynna get good at pythoon
LiIDrunk: in game or waiting or gone
l_mbert: You don‘t need „window.“, don‘t know if anyone said this :D
Nelzex: do people actually make react native apps for android etc
Fr3fou: i have sorta
Fr3fou: for 2 hackathons
Fr3fou: which i both won 😎
Nelzex: oh nice
Nelzex: litty
KNOOKEL_HEAD: @l_mbert its the same thing but yeah
Nelzex: where do you live
Fr3fou: bulgaria
Nelzex: aint no hackathons near me
Nelzex: oh shit
Nelzex: i aint got no excuse :D
treestompztv: list.map
Fr3fou: there's one every few months
l_mbert: @knookel_head yeah, but it‘s obsolete :D
Nelzex: is it online or in person?
Fr3fou: in person
Nelzex: nice
Fr3fou: have had to travel 4 hours for some
Nelzex: oh right
treestompztv: a.map(x => console.log(x)) is preferred I think
Fr3fou: worth it tho
Nelzex: ye it sounds like a lot of fun
Fr3fou: and stressful
Fr3fou: kek
haxiwage: is he using webrtc?
kzonixcomua: yes
kzonixcomua: peerjs
anguscupcake: @georgehotz how do u have infinite energy
unique_ptr_: @haxiwage just peerjs
Fr3fou: he's on drugs @anguscupcake
haxiwage: okok
that_turns_me_on: anguscupcake high testosterone
Nelzex: is there a way to make android apps in python?
Fr3fou: for in loop @georgehotz
Fr3fou: oh
Fr3fou: if that's what yo uwant, sure
Nelzex: hah
Nelzex: i want projects to practice python
Nelzex: but idk what
Nelzex: throw some my way if u have
MoProject: its no good to charge at 100%
LaneBoyR6: Tic Tac Toe game ?
Fr3fou: implement a ghetto blockchain @Nelzex
Nelzex: i was thinking tic tac toe
Fr3fou: with p2p
Nelzex: ghetto alt coin lookin ass
Fr3fou: yea
Fr3fou: it's fun tho
Nelzex: iota lookin ass
Fr3fou: i've done jahcoin
Nelzex: aight bet
LiIDrunk: you also gotta remove those who already joined a game
W1lkins: use componentWillUnmount?
KNOOKEL_HEAD: ^
anguscupcake: @fr3fou what drugs
Nelzex: how tf do u use vim
ragemaster999: @Fr3fou can i invest?
Nelzex: shits difficult
W1lkins: delete x;
W1lkins: LUL
Jannnik: delete obj.prop
reaganchisholm: reaganchisholm subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 2 months, currently on a 1 month streak! :)
anguscupcake: kratom?
LiIDrunk: you also gotta remove those who already joined a game
AnAnonymousCheerer: Anon1
Ziv0: ocr
erlsek: github
Noxique: is GitHub blocked in china?
claymorehack1: yes
chaprio1: Is there something unblocked in China? monkaS
Noxique: are there any alternatives?
Noxique: o.o
LoLskiller1: yes, use vpn, then use github
Nelzex: ye
syska: pog
LiIDrunk: add a replay button
chocolatechp: me
iFun: Lol no
iFun: GitHub is not blocked in China
NV17: Is that a bed in the kitchen?
Caene: link :)
kelbs: didn't copy first letter of link
archeadis: @georgehotz how do you connect to the IPFS on port 5001?
wiseai: china 5Head
Maw3rick: @Caene https://cloudflare-ipfs.com/ipfs/QmaVi2KEGhvuaK82YCP4SmARMCUV8sJw1f1AWQjeJHnurD/
LiIDrunk: add a play again button for rematch bw same users
archeadis: how do you run it?
kelbs: You didn't copy it. Put the 'h' in http into your link
Caene: @Maw3rick Thanks
Maw3rick: Np
savlon: I know this says simple skills but come on, this is childs play... get on with it
Maw3rick: Hell yeah
lolcoolkat: yeah you forgot an h in the url when you copied it
NV17: which web browser is the best?
okkessh: why was I unable to connect to you
okkessh: while you are debugging
archeadis: is it go-ipfs?
georgehotz: https://cloudflare-ipfs.com/ipfs/QmRoBbkZCPKp7wK36uA3u5xBsBjzJnvGetioGn2pRxwBG3/
Fr3fou: have you tried implementing IPFS yourself is it fun @georgehotz
okkessh: dont you use the peer.js default api ke y
Arksam: LUL
W1lkins: I don't see any user list
httpsdubdubdotcomm: this is cool
httpsdubdubdotcomm: i enjoy
Caene: I won one!
Santiago_LHC: I'm adding some sick CSS styles to PR
MuscleMario: lol
LiIDrunk: no user list
LiIDrunk: showing up
unique_ptr_: mama! my peer id is on the screen!! mama got the camera!
KrrSplat: KrrSplat subscribed at Tier 1.
Zhrun: Put user count
johnny_thehobo: damn he actually learned react in 2 hours and made tic tac toe online
KNOOKEL_HEAD: LUL
schadowman: damn this actually works so well LUL
Nelzex: u need to clear the board when game finishes
Maw3rick: Gotcha MATE
Lugueiro: send the link pls
iFun: iFun subscribed with Twitch Prime.
altic: 5Head
chocolatechp: lol
chaprio1: Gz Pog
treestompztv: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
Maw3rick: ahhaahhaha
ᅟᅟᅟᅟ: LUL
Ricoello: LUL
Bioaim7: pog
Maw3rick: @georgehotz WP
razr22: ???????????????????/
iFun: lol
fear_ep: LOL
razr22: lmao
johnny_thehobo: get pwned
MuscleMario: Staged
LiIDrunk: lol
KrrSplat: nice
dorkmo: Corgo1
savlon: are u on drugs?
wiseai: PRO GAMER
chaprio1: paid actors smh
tornpaperyoyos: let it be known that george is now only 1-1 at tic tac toe LUL and a lot of draws
Brohanson: limmySteel
KNOOKEL_HEAD: absolute dogshit software PogChamp
lolcoolkat: need a way to leave the current game.. cause the person I connected to isnt playing :(
KrrSplat: giggity
razr22: i missed the link
lolcoolkat: https://cloudflare-ipfs.com/ipfs/QmRoBbkZCPKp7wK36uA3u5xBsBjzJnvGetioGn2pRxwBG3
KNOOKEL_HEAD: immutable dogshit software LUL
treestompztv: gg
razr22: thanks
zeroeagle1: part 2 twitch p2p chat?
Arksam: StinkyCheese
ragemaster999: gg
wiseai: what chair you use for coding? Kappa
httpsdubdubdotcomm: cya @georgehotz thanks for doin stuff
martinstuessy: @georgehotz check the PR :)
KNOOKEL_HEAD: LUL
xrealyy: more stuff like this please @georgehotz
bluedick69: its broken in firefox
NV17: GITHUB Link?
yum72: I get no users
VOR0R: check PRs
Caene: Next stream: Guess Drawing Game, 5man lobbies. Kappa
syska: i won lol
georgehotz: https://github.com/geohot/twitchtactoe
unique_ptr_: now i have some silicon valley flashback
bluedick69: fix in firefox!!!
wiseai: PJSugar bathroom break
lolcoolkat: nothotdog Kappa
ragemaster999: you may or may not play against bots right now
LiIDrunk: did you tried wasd keyboard
Vesh: cooking stream george?
LiIDrunk: i saw it in a video
savlon: did u have playstation @georgehotz
KNOOKEL_HEAD: if you use firefox just dont use firefox
ppnn123w: waiting for Rick and Morty
okkessh: what api key did you use
MuscleMario: Wuts for lunch?
savlon: hack
lolcoolkat: NotLikeThis
okkessh: in peer.js
martinstuessy: @georgehotz most life changing PR in your repo bro
colanzio5: @georgehotz do you think you'll do anything with redux?
Maw3rick: This was really fun stream SeemsGood keep up the good work!
alreye: @georgehotz you bug.. the opposite player got two tries before I went
savlon: did u hack playstation???? @georgehotz
ragemaster999: you may or may not play against bots right now
KNOOKEL_HEAD: you should do React more often SeemsGood
Divulger1: <message deleted>
unique_ptr_: now make some skins and get millioner :D
LiIDrunk: mac and cheese for subscriber milestone maybe ??
zakonegrusha: hackerman stream
zakonegrusha: still a skid tho
okkessh: which api key did you use
Vesh: PogChamp
wiseai: PogU
anguscupcake: what u use for energy
YouPowerRush: sikk
MuscleMario: Cooking streams
okkessh: then why couldnt I connect to you
Caene: you could easily apply for partnership and most likely get it. :P
Vesh: did u apply for partner yet? cause if u dont apply u dont get it
rektiw0w: we had twitch staff earlier in this stream, so there might be a chance
Artistxtv: how ur not a twitch partner is beyond me
okkessh: this whole time I just tried to make a connection
dawgwhisper007: yeahh
LeeRoy_227: LeeRoy_227 subscribed with Twitch Prime.
NV17: How does make money?
unique_ptr_: u need to stream more for partnership, your viewer number is great
erichtp: if u become partner can you stream on youtube?
zakonegrusha: how do I play tictac
KNOOKEL_HEAD: PogChamp HACKER
johnny_thehobo: can you do a stream where you pull one pleb and teach him programming?
dawgwhisper007: @georgehotz cooleratiz
MuscleMario: yeah, gimmie my twitter handle
zakonegrusha: guys how can I play tic tac
anguscupcake: how do I shot web
Vesh: me
rektiw0w: me :)
Abnormmall: me :)
MuscleMario: LOL
Caene: probably many here LUL
MuscleMario: I got a pleb for u
Zabak378: me :)
gutschilino: me :)
Divulger1: I would be a pleb
yaus_baus: im pleb
zakonegrusha: HOW TO PLAY TIC TAC
Vesh: id volunteer in a hearbeat
UzeezU: Computationalist manifesto
wiseai: MAKE COMPUTERS GREAT AGAIN Kappa
Lythaslol: Lythaslol subscribed with Twitch Prime.
unique_ptr_: dear 07b136egp8c40000 pls move :(
ragemaster999: you may or may not play against bots right now
LiIDrunk: some rap for the outro
zakonegrusha: is this just a localhost things hes hosting or can I play
yaus_baus: freestyle
MuscleMario: @yaus_baus sup
thedavosfinger: hacker ganster
yaus_baus: @MuscleMario yoyo
zakonegrusha: @georgehotz what is the link to it tho
KNOOKEL_HEAD: LUL
colanzio5: @georgehotz do you think you'll do bigger projects with react and redux? Heard you complaining about state being in view components earlier...
unique_ptr_: 07b136egp8c40000 sorry, i won, next time better :) i think we should implement a chat for this xD
yaus_baus: bye george
Divulger1: he is using HHKB Keybaord
itzalexpl_: Bye :(
YouPowerRush: bey
LiIDrunk: bbye
gmabreak: <3
KNOOKEL_HEAD: thank you man!
ᅟᅟᅟᅟ: :) /
Vesh: bye
httpsdubdubdotcomm: @georgehotz enjoy your day! cheer dude
anguscupcake: redux is state management in js
treestompztv: bye :)
Maw3rick: Cya
kingkong3211: bye
matejsninja: bb
Divulger1: bye
schadowman: bai
kingkong3211: ciao
mixxaww: BibleThump bye
TheDrewPeacock: mizkifSat mizkifSleeper
frankytex: redux is what you squeeze out when you can't program in another language
Zabak378: <3
data_day_life: platySUH